<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Andaze Ltd.</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Andaze Ltd.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andaze.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Arai A.</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/professional-images/1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 10:55:10 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/professional-images/1/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Renewal of Corporate Website</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/news/news_1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 09:38:56 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/news/news_1/</guid><description>Thank you for visiting the website of Andaze Ltd. We have made a major renewal of our website starting June 2022.
In this renewal, we have reviewed the design and page structure, and added new contents.
We will continue to make further improvements and provide useful information so that many of you will be able to use our website.</description></item><item><title>Top Message</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/message/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:02:12 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/message/</guid><description>Top Message Andaze was founded in 2016. The impetus for the company&amp;rsquo;s founding came from my trip to India in 2011. What I experienced there, what I felt firsthand, and what I wondered about&amp;hellip;. As a result of my search for what I could do and the pursuit of my ideals, Andaze was born. In recent years, sustainability has been positioned as an important factor in management strategy, and we have been working to provide our employees, who come from a variety of backgrounds including nationalities, with a diverse and personalized work style that allows them to work fully remotely, and to accelerate the business value generated from this work style.</description></item><item><title>AI（Artificial Intelligence）</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/artificial-intelligence/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/services/artificial-intelligence/</guid><description>AI (Artificial Intelligence) Providing highly accurate AI solutions that further enhance business value Andaze&amp;rsquo;s AI solutions, based on our strength of abundant knowledge and advanced technology, are highly accurate and contribute significantly to business efficiency. Our shared team, which is involved from consulting to development and operation, achieves high-level AI development. We further enhance the quality of our solutions by repeatedly improving them through design illustrations and prototypes that are easy to visualize.</description></item><item><title>AZURE BOT FRAMEWORK</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/azure-bot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/azure-bot/</guid><description>AZURE BOT FRAMEWORK Chatbot Development&amp;quot; for 24-hour automated response to help increase customer satisfaction Overview A chatbot is an &amp;ldquo;automatic conversation system&amp;rdquo; that combines &amp;ldquo;chat&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;robot. They can reply to inquiries often received from users at internal help desks, customer support, etc., in place of staff using tools such as LINE. Andaze&amp;rsquo;s chatbot development is characterized by a high degree of accuracy that contributes to increased operational efficiency and customer satisfaction.</description></item><item><title>Top Message</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/company/message/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/company/message/</guid><description>Top Message As a true technology supporter who also understands business strategy, we contribute to transformation through the use of digital technology. Andaze is a venture company created by spin-outs of leading professionals in various fields ranging from technology development to consulting.
Since its inception, Andaze has always been on the lookout for trends and has been generous in its use of superior technology.
All members of the team are highly motivated and function as players in the industry.</description></item><item><title>Ashish M.</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/professional-images/2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 11:18:54 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/professional-images/2/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Human Rights Policy</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/human-rights/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:02:12 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/human-rights/</guid><description>Human Rights Policy Andaze&amp;rsquo;s management philosophy is &amp;ldquo;Bringing innovation to Japan through global and superior technology. Andaze&amp;rsquo;s management philosophy is to &amp;ldquo;Bring innovation to Japan through global and superior technology. Based on this philosophy, we will make company-wide efforts to respect the human rights of all people involved in our business activities. Respect for International Human Rights Norms We understand and respect as a minimum the human rights described in the International Bill of Human Rights, including the Universal Declaration of Human Rights, and the core labor standards of the International Labor Organization (ILO) Declaration on Fundamental Principles and Rights at Work.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/company/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/company/about/</guid><description>About Us Company Name Andaze Ltd. Location head office
10-3, Kojimachi 2-chome, Chiyoda-ku, Tokyo development base
5-1, Kojimachi 2-chome, Chiyoda-ku, Tokyo WeWork Hanzomon PREXSouth 2F Established April 2016 Fiscal year: March Capital 20,000,000 Yen Representative Mina Arai Bank Sumitomo Mitsui Banking Corporation, Hibiya Branch The Japan Net Bank, Limited, Head Office Sales Department Approved Standards Information Security Management System（ISO27001) Quality Management System（ISO9001） Phone number 03-3230-0401 Website https://andaze.com Business (1) Diagnosis, guidance, and consulting of management information systems for various companies (2) Consulting on business improvement and IT strategy (3) Investment in information and telecommunications businesses and consulting on mergers, alliances, and transfers of business rights of these companies (4) Planning, development, import and export of computer software (5) Production and sale of publications and electronic content (6) Consulting and advertising agency services related to employee recruitment for various companies (7) Development of personnel systems and educational programs, and planning and implementation of education and training (8) Buying, selling, holding and managing securities (9) Investment advisory services related to securities, and all businesses incidental and related to the above</description></item><item><title>AZURE AI</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/azure-ai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/azure-ai/</guid><description>AZURE AI AI Machine Learning Development&amp;quot; for high prediction accuracy and improved business value Overview In recent years, with the spread of smartphones and IoT, a large amount of data has been accumulated. Analyzing this data by humans takes an enormous amount of time and effort. On the other hand, AI machine learning makes it possible to discover regularities that cannot be found by human power and to finish the analysis work in an instant.</description></item><item><title>Cloud</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/services/cloud/</guid><description>Cloud Computing Supporting the best cloud deployment for your digital strategy Cloud computing is essential for DX. In addition, the adoption of the most appropriate cloud service is required depending on the customer&amp;rsquo;s business challenges and system environment. Andaze will develop a detailed migration roadmap in accordance with the customer&amp;rsquo;s industry, company size, and requirements. We not only realize the migration of existing systems to the cloud, but also provide access to them under safer and more secure security, which will be a driving force to promote the transformation of your company in the wake of digitalization.</description></item><item><title>Fujimaki Y.</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/professional-images/3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 11:38:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/professional-images/3/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Environmental Policy</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/environmental-policy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:02:12 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/environmental-policy/</guid><description>Environmental Policy We at Andaze have established the following Environmental Policy as a guideline to fulfill our responsibility toward the realization of a sustainable society. Resource Recycling Initiatives In order to shift from a consumption-oriented to a recycling-oriented economy and to pass on a sustainable global environment to future generations, we will promote initiatives to effectively utilize resources throughout the entire process from procurement to use and disposal of products and systems.</description></item><item><title>Consulting</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/consulting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/services/consulting/</guid><description>Consulting Experienced consultants with a high level of expertise DX enables our clients to transform all aspects of their corporate activities for the better. Andaze&amp;rsquo;s shared team of highly specialized digital consultants provides a comprehensive range of services, from strategy development and implementation to customer support, to help you design a digital strategy that works for you.
Why choose Andaze? (1) We understand your business challenges and needs, and create effective solutions ・Our goal is not to provide solutions, but to provide consulting services that solve the issues our clients face.</description></item><item><title>Dynamics365</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/dynamics365/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/dynamics365/</guid><description>Dynamics365 Introduction of Customer Relationship Management CRM&amp;quot; for accurate analysis of information on existing customers for sales promotion. Overview CRM (Customer Relationship Management) is an IT tool that has been introduced in many successful companies. Now is the time when developing new customers is important, while correctly understanding existing customers and implementing the most appropriate strategy for each of them will pay off. Andaze helps you visualize the analysis of customer information with its superior solution Dynamics365 so that you can optimize your outreach to your users.</description></item><item><title>History</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/company/history/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/company/history/</guid><description>History 2011 Representative Arai came to India 2015 Returned from India. Started preparing to establish a company 2016 Founding of Andaze Ltd. 2018 Certified as a Microsoft Silver Partner 2019 Head office relocated from Toranomon to Kojimachi 2019 Capital Increase to 10 million yen 2020 Establish development base at WeWork Hanzomon 2020 Certified as a Microsoft Gold Partner 2021 Obtained ISO 9001 and ISO 27001 certification 2021 Capital Increase to 20 million yen</description></item><item><title>Keval C.</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/professional-images/4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 11:43:15 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/professional-images/4/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Effective use of resources</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/resources/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:02:12 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/resources/</guid><description>Effective use of resources We at Andaze believe that it is important for people living on the earth to address environmental issues such as climate change. We are working to reduce our environmental impact with the aim of achieving a sustainable society. Promoting a paperless work environment We are eliminating conventional paper-based meetings and distribution of materials to the greatest extent possible. We place emphasis on digital meetings using monitors and other devices both inside and outside the company.</description></item><item><title>AZURE B2C</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/azure-b2c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/azure-b2c/</guid><description>AZURE B2C Superior Subject Authentication Service to Protect Sensitive Information from Hackers Overview Hacking and hijacking of applications can be a major social problem if personal information such as IDs and passwords are leaked to outside parties. AZURE B2C prevents data leakage and provides high security services. We work on system development while placing emphasis on the handling of personal information.
Effects of Introduction (1) Support millions of users and billions of authentications per day Securely handles billions of logins per day, preventing information leaks that could be fatal to the company.</description></item><item><title>Management Philosophy</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/company/philosophy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/company/philosophy/</guid><description>Management Philosophy Supporting corporate DX at the forefront of technology. In this era, it is no longer possible to compete only on product quality and price.
What is needed to survive in the competitive market of the future is DX,
which drives business value at an accelerated pace.
Andaze contributes to the creation of innovative innovations
that add value to businesses and overturn existing business models.
Professionals with diverse skills create new added value</description></item><item><title>UI/UX Design</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/design/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/services/design/</guid><description>UI/UX Design Supporting the development of products that are comfortable, pleasant, and easy to use Beautiful design, easy-to-use functions, and intuitive colors and tastes. Andaze expresses UI and UX in the best possible way based on our extensive experience and knowledge. We leverage our high level of expertise to support development that places the highest priority on the customer experience while adhering to the client&amp;rsquo;s requirements. Experience the best UI/UX design with meaning and value in every single piece.</description></item><item><title>Abhishek S.</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/professional-images/5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 11:44:07 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/professional-images/5/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Contribution to society based on our corporate philosophy</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/contribution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:02:12 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/contribution/</guid><description>Contribution to society based on our corporate philosophy Andaze is committed to &amp;ldquo;Bringing innovation to Japan through global and superior technology. We at Andaze are committed to promoting sustainable initiatives for our business partners, the people we serve, and society as a whole based on our corporate philosophy of &amp;ldquo;Bringing Innovation to Japan through Global Excellence. Diversity and Inclusion We value human resources above all else. There is no discrimination or distinction.</description></item><item><title>BLAZOR WEB</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/blazor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/blazor/</guid><description>BLAZOR WEB SPA application development&amp;quot; that can provide comfortable web expression Overview SPA (Single Page Application) is a system in which contents are switched one after another on a single web page. The next content can be displayed without having to click on a link and reload the page. Andaze provides comfortable web expressions that run crisply, not to mention improved visuals and usability. This leads to increased user satisfaction.</description></item><item><title>Recruitment agency services</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/recruit-agency/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/services/recruit-agency/</guid><description>Recruitment Agency Services Total support from recruiting to hiring and training Andaze utilizes AI to select the most effective media and methods among diversifying recruitment methods. We also provide a series of HR services on behalf of our clients, from consulting to recruitment planning, job posting, scheduling, and post-hire training, etc. We support strategic recruitment activities by analyzing market trends and information obtained through our professional knowledge cultivated by supporting more than 200 companies in their recruitment, and through collaboration with various agencies and partner companies.</description></item><item><title>Kanamori.S</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/professional-images/6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 11:45:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/professional-images/6/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Information Security Management System</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/information-security-management/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:02:12 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/information-security-management/</guid><description>Information Security Management System We at Andaze recognize that ensuring the security of our customers&amp;rsquo; information and personal information is a top management priority. Andaze has obtained ISO 27001 certification, the international standard for information security management systems (ISMS), to ensure the security management, confidentiality, integrity, and availability of information.</description></item><item><title>New Business Service Development</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/service-develop/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/services/service-develop/</guid><description>New Business Service Development Support from new business to expansion using existing systems From the digitization of analog information such as documents to new businesses that create business models from scratch, the possibilities for DX are endless. Andaze&amp;rsquo;s one-stop shared team with over 20 years of experience handles everything from strategic planning to implementation, operation, and maintenance of services utilizing superior technology. More objective and neutral. We support your digital innovation within the feasible cost range.</description></item><item><title>SIGNALR</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/signalr/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/signalr/</guid><description>SIGNALR Interactive Communication Web Service Development&amp;quot; to make users&amp;rsquo; site browsing more comfortable Overview For example, real-time information, such as stock price charts and chats, is required as a product value. However, with conventional systems, information must be kept up-to-date through &amp;ldquo;periodic screen updates. This results in high communication volume, flickering screens, and other problems that can lead to a low level of user satisfaction.
Therefore, we recommend &amp;ldquo;interactive web services.</description></item><item><title>Basic Policy on Information Security</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/information-security-policy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:02:12 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/information-security-policy/</guid><description>Basic Policy on Information Security Andaze is committed to ensuring, maintaining, and utilizing information security, one of the most important issues in our business activities, in accordance with our corporate philosophy of &amp;ldquo;Bringing innovation to Japan through global and superior technology. We, Andaze Corporation, have established and implemented the following Basic Policy on Information Security based on our belief that it is our responsibility to protect all information assets we handle in order to ensure, maintain, and utilize information security, which is one of the most important issues in our business activities.</description></item><item><title>DEVEXPRESS</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/devexpress/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/devexpress/</guid><description>DEVEXPRESS UX-focused application development&amp;quot; that enhances the value of services through user satisfaction Overview Satisfaction and pleasure obtained through services and products. Such value that users experience and feel is called &amp;ldquo;UX (user experience). A decade ago, high functionality was enough to attract people&amp;rsquo;s interest and attention, but in recent years, when material wealth has been achieved, more and more people are willing to pay for &amp;ldquo;experience&amp;rdquo; in addition to functionality.</description></item><item><title>Shared Team</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/shared/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/services/shared/</guid><description>Shared Team A diverse team of highly skilled professionals Shared Team is a group of professionals from various fields. Each consultant, PM, and engineer takes the initiative in steering the project to achieve the goals. By not having a fixed number of team members, all Andaze staff naturally understand the client&amp;rsquo;s technical information, regardless of the size of the project. We are able to provide our knowledge as needed. We do not limit the scope of work, but rather offer a flexible &amp;ldquo;quasi-contract&amp;rdquo; style that allows us to work flexibly according to your company&amp;rsquo;s situation, from strategic planning to design, operation, and helpdesk services.</description></item><item><title>モバイルコンテンツ高速化 / AMP WEB</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/amp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/amp/</guid><description>AMP WEB Mobile Content Acceleration&amp;quot; to reduce the waiting time until a web page is displayed Overview AMP (Accelerated Mobile Pages, commonly known as amp) is a standard jointly launched by Google and Twitter to enable mobile users to comfortably view websites. The literal translation means &amp;ldquo;faster pages for mobile.
AMP enables search engines to read information on web pages ahead of time and direct links from search results to them, so that data can be displayed without having to jump to the page each time.</description></item><item><title>HUGO WEB</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/hugo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/hugo/</guid><description>HUGO WEB Static Website Development for fast page loading with secure security Overview You want to increase the display speed of your web pages, or you want to have a solid security measure, or you do not want to update information in real time&amp;hellip;. Static website development is useful for websites with such characteristics. There are three main reasons why static websites are attracting attention today.
Effects of Introduction (1) Security Most CMS (Content Management System = a system that allows web content to be updated without specialized knowledge) are regularly upgraded.</description></item><item><title>AZURE COSMOS DATABASE</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/database/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/database/</guid><description>AZURE COSMOS DATABASE NOSQL Database Development&amp;quot; for storing huge databases with data optimization Overview Database file size is getting bigger and bigger. In order to handle exponentially increasing data, such as real-time analysis while maintaining such a large amount of data, &amp;ldquo;data optimization&amp;rdquo; is necessary. Therefore, an increasing number of companies are using NOSQL (abbreviation of Not only SQL) as a complement to the conventional RDB (Relational DataBase Management System / Relational DataBase Management System ).</description></item><item><title>AZURE TABLE STORAGE</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/storage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/storage/</guid><description>AZURE TABLE STORAGE Big Data Analytics Development&amp;quot; for inexpensive and speedy analysis of exponentially growing data Overview The recent proliferation of smartphones has led to the emergence of massive amounts of data. Moreover, even home appliances such as refrigerators, air conditioners, and vacuum cleaners are connected to the Internet and continue to generate new data. The amount of data held by companies is growing exponentially.
In order to store and process such large and varied data, problems of capacity, cost, and speed have been a constant concern until now.</description></item></channel></rss>