<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>implementing-dynamics-365 on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/implementing-dynamics-365/</link><description>Recent content in implementing-dynamics-365 on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/implementing-dynamics-365/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Dynamics 365 licensing costs</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/implementing-dynamics-365/type-license-dynamics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/implementing-dynamics-365/type-license-dynamics/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous chapter, we have discussed the uses, functions, and usage scenarios of Dynamics 365. It is a highly functional product with seamless integration with existing Microsoft products. However, the appeal of Dynamics 365 is not only in its features.
How much is the basic cost of a Dynamics 365 license? In this section, we will introduce the cost of Dynamics 365 licenses in comparison with other CRM systems.</description></item><item><title>Let's think about the implementation schedule and procedures for Dynamics 365</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/implementing-dynamics-365/deployment-schedule-dynamics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/implementing-dynamics-365/deployment-schedule-dynamics/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Once the purpose of implementing CRM and Dynamics 365 is clarified, it will be easier to consider the next step, which is how soon to implement them.
In the process of clarifying the purpose of implementing Dynamics 365, you may have made a list of both &amp;ldquo;need to be able to&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;want to be able to&amp;rdquo; operations.
It is important to consider the implementation schedule.</description></item><item><title>Purchasing a Dynamics 365 license</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/implementing-dynamics-365/purchase-license-dynamics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/implementing-dynamics-365/purchase-license-dynamics/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn So far, we have been preparing for the implementation of Dynamics 365.
Now that we have a schedule and a rough estimate of the cost, we would like to start using Dynamics 365. The first thing you need to do is to purchase a license. This is very basic, but if you don&amp;rsquo;t purchase a license, you can&amp;rsquo;t proceed.
Purchase a license for Dynamics 365 First, proceed to purchase a license from the following website.</description></item></channel></rss>