<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>maintaining-dynamics-365 on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/</link><description>Recent content in maintaining-dynamics-365 on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dynamics 365 Instance NORMALITY</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/normality-of-instance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/normality-of-instance/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn We have been managing instances of Dynamics 365 by operating the Management Center. Now we will introduce how to manage the instances to make sure they are working properly.
Checking Instance Integrity To check the normality of the instance, open Service Normality. If the Normalcy column is set to &amp;ldquo;Normal Service&amp;rdquo;, then the instance is normal.
Check the storage area of the instance You can also check the storage space to be used.</description></item><item><title>Backup and Restore of Dynamics 365 Instances</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/backup-restore-instance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/backup-restore-instance/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn This article is the last one about Dynamics instances. In this article, we will show you how to backup and restore an instance.
Backing up an instance In Dynamics 365, backups are automatically taken on a per-instance basis.
The frequency of acquisition is once a day, and the backup retention period is 3 days (maximum). Expired backups will be deleted automatically.
Obtain backups manually (on-demand backups) If you want to make a backup manually, click &amp;ldquo;New Backup&amp;rdquo; to make a backup.</description></item><item><title>Update your Dynamics 365!</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/update-dynamics-instance-to-ver9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/update-dynamics-instance-to-ver9/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn It has been a while since Dynamcis 365 version 9 (July 2017 update) was released in July 2017. The trial version of Dynamcis 365 is now version 9, and those who are using version 8 may be in the minority. I think the number of people using version 8 is getting smaller.
As a matter of fact, my client&amp;rsquo;s Dynamics 365 was running on version 8 until recently.</description></item><item><title>Creating a Dynamics 365 Process</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/dynamics-365-process-use/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/dynamics-365-process-use/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Dynamics 365 has a feature called Processes that allows you to model your business methods and automate specific processes. There are four main types of processes. (The following is taken from the technical information)
Workflow. Use this process to model and automate real-world business processes. These processes can be configured to run in the background or in real time, and can require user input as needed. Workflow processes can be started automatically based on specified criteria or manually by the user.</description></item><item><title>Basic operation of Dynamics 365 processes</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-more-of-workflow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-more-of-workflow/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous article, &amp;ldquo;Creating a Process in Dynamics 365&amp;rdquo;, we have discussed the steps to create a workflow for a process.
Update the record In the previous article, we gave you a simple way to update records, so this time we will apply it.
Update the value of the associated record This is done by changing the entity to be updated after adding the step of updating the record.</description></item><item><title>Using Dynamics 365 business rules</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-business-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-business-rules/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Dynamics 365 has a feature called Business Rules. Normally, Javascript implementation is required to hide fields or perform operations according to conditions on a form. However, this feature eliminates the need for script implementation and allows users to easily set up the rules required for their business.
The following can be achieved with business rules.
By combining conditions and actions, business rules can be used to perform the following operations</description></item><item><title>Managing Dynamics 365 Entities</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/create-new-entity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/create-new-entity/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Learn how to manage Dynamics 365 entities, including creating, editing, and deleting them.
About Entities When you set up Dynamics 365, you are provided with basic entities such as customer company, customer representative, sales case, and activities. Each entity manages company information, representative information, business meetings, and activities of business meetings (phone calls, emails, appointments, tasks, etc.).
It also allows you to create custom entities for your organization and associate them with default entities for flexible management of your business data.</description></item><item><title>Using Dynamics 365 Calculated Fields</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-calculation-fields/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-calculation-fields/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In this article, I will give a brief introduction to calculated fields in Dynamics 365.
About calculated fields Calculated fields are a type of field in Dynamics 365 that can be used for the following data types
One line of text Option Set Two options integer decimal number Currency Date and time By using calculated fields, you can change the value of a field depending on the condition of If Else, calculate it by a function, or get the data of a related entity via a lookup field.</description></item><item><title>Managing a Dynamics 365 Instance</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/manage-dynamics-instance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/manage-dynamics-instance/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at what you can do in the Dynamics 365 admin center.
Managing Instances Instances allow you to manage the currently configured instances (production and sandbox (*1)) and install solutions for the instances. In the case of Plan 1 license, a free sandbox instance is provided.
(*2)
(*1) What is a sandbox?
A sandbox instance is a non-production environment instance of Microsoft Dynamics 365 (online).</description></item><item><title>Customization of Dynamics 365 entities and option sets</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/customize-entity-option-sets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/customize-entity-option-sets/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn From the Dynamics 365 menu, click on Settings - Customize System to open the Solution Explorer as shown below.
Then expand Components and you will see a customizable list.
Let&amp;rsquo;s discuss some of the typical components here.
entity The first one is Entities, where you can configure basic entity-related settings. If you expand the &amp;ldquo;Entities&amp;rdquo; component, you will see a list of default entities. (Left side of the screen below)</description></item><item><title>Customize Dynamics 365 web resources and processes</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/customize-web-resource-process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/customize-web-resource-process/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous article, we talked about &amp;ldquo;entities&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;option sets&amp;rdquo; rather than system customization. What other customizations can be done?
In this article, I will provide an overview of web resources, processes, dashboards, and reports.
Web Resources Web resources can be used to create HTML files, Javascript, CSS, XML and Silverlight applications, as well as image files such as icons for Dynamics 365. The content you create with web resources can be used in forms, sitemaps, etc.</description></item><item><title>Recommended third-party solutions</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/whats-3rd-party-solutions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/whats-3rd-party-solutions/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn The beauty of Dynamics 365 is that there are many solutions available to assist and augment its functionality, but what solutions can further extend the capabilities of Dynamics 365?
In this article, I would like to introduce some of the solutions I have used that have been particularly effective after installation.
(*Note) Third-party solutions are not necessarily solutions that Microsoft guarantees to work. This blog is only for information sharing, so please import at your own risk with sufficient verification when importing in your own environment.</description></item><item><title>Countermeasures against infinite loops in workflow processes</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-workflow-process-loop/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-workflow-process-loop/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn The workflow process in Dynamics 365 is a useful feature that allows you to do many things without coding, from updating, creating and deleting data to assigning and sending emails. In addition to the default workflow processes, you can import third-party workflow solutions such as those found in Workflow Heroes, which allow you to create workflow processes for many of your users&amp;rsquo; needs, such as record sharing, date and decimal arithmetic, and more.</description></item><item><title>Changes to the method of applying major updates [2019.08]</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/changed_update_policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/changed_update_policy/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn To be honest, I think the major update of Dynamics 365 is an update that makes the operation and maintenance department cry.
To support the update
Wait for the instance to become eligible for updates. Once an instance is eligible for an update, set a candidate update date for verification in the sandbox. Make two schedules to prepare for the case that the proposed date does not run as planned.</description></item><item><title>Adjust the sitemap in the settings</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-privilege-to-settingsitemap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-privilege-to-settingsitemap/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn When you create a Dynamics 365 app, it will be created as a unified interface (mobile-driven app) due to the current integration with Power Apps. This is where the advanced settings can be opened to the general public, but I found out that the settings can be fine-tuned, so I will describe them here.
Settings menu visible to the general public Even ordinary users with little to no privileges can use</description></item></channel></rss>