<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Solution on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/</link><description>Recent content in Solution on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AZURE BOT FRAMEWORK</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/azure-bot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/azure-bot/</guid><description>Why are “chatbots” getting so much attention? A chatbot is a combination of chat and bot, which means &amp;ldquo;a robot that talks.&amp;rdquo; It is not a physical robot but a communication tool for companies.
User benefits
Feel free to contact us Reduces call waiting time Corporate benefits
Reduced man-hours for operators and reduced turnover rate Repeat bot learning to improve service Logs help improve business Even in work style reforms aimed at improving labor productivity, there is an urgent need to improve work efficiency, especially for small and medium-sized enterprises.</description></item><item><title>AZURE AI</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/azure-ai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/azure-ai/</guid><description>Why is “Machine Learning” getting so much attention? With the spread of smartphones, a large amount of data has started to appear. As it is, it requires a great deal of cost and time to process complicated data, but now it is possible to realize by machine learning that &amp;ldquo;calculation of analysis results with speed and accuracy that cannot be achieved by humans&amp;rdquo;. It was.
Pros of machine learning
-Prediction value is calculated by learning features -Select multiple reproducible models by applying multiple algorithms -Clustering classifies features to improve prediction accuracy</description></item><item><title>Dynamics365</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/dynamics365/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/dynamics365/</guid><description>Why is “Customer Relationship Management” getting so much attention? It is important to continue to cultivate new customers, but it is said to be an era in which we aim to increase sales as a whole by taking more care of our current customers. We need a system that manages information about customer relationships by keeping a history of contact with customers by the system.
Purpose of CRM Increase new customers Increase repeat rate from existing customers Increase service unit price Lower costs The customer relationship management system can centrally manage information about prospects, sales, and after-sales service.</description></item><item><title>AZURE B2C</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/azure-b2c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/azure-b2c/</guid><description>Why is &amp;ldquo;B2C development service&amp;rdquo; important? The awareness of social crisis has increased in response to the recent leak of customer information. Regarding future information leaks, it will be obligatory to report to the Personal Information Protection Committee and notify the person in question.
In B2C development, the system is constructed with emphasis on subject authentication and handling of personal information.
B2C development benefits
Provides user sign-up, sign-in and profile management Compatible with iOS, Android, .</description></item><item><title>BLAZOR WEB</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/blazor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/blazor/</guid><description>Why is “single page application (SPA)” getting so much attention? This is because, instead of reading the contents for each page from the browser, you can change the functions and contents by replacing only the necessary data. SPAs can greatly improve the user&amp;rsquo;s impression of your application. It not only improves appearance and usability, but also provides a crisp movement. Slack and Google Map web pages are well known examples of using SPA.</description></item><item><title>SIGNALR</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/signalr/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/signalr/</guid><description>Why is the &amp;ldquo;two-way communication web service&amp;rdquo; attracting attention? For information such as stock charts and chats, real-time properties are required as product value. In the old system, the information was updated with a mechanism such as periodic screen updates. It was not a good user experience because the amount of communication for that purpose increased and the screen flickered.
A two-way web service is a mechanism that allows users to browse information stored in the system in real time.</description></item><item><title>DEVEXPRESS</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/devexpress/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/devexpress/</guid><description>Why is the &amp;ldquo;user experience&amp;rdquo; getting so much attention? UX (user experience) is translated as &amp;ldquo;user experience&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;user experience&amp;rdquo;, and is the collective term for experiences and emotions that users can experience when they contact or use a company, product or service.
Due to technological advances, the functions and features of products have become indistinguishable from other companies&amp;rsquo; products and services. Up until now, we have been able to attract people&amp;rsquo;s attention by launching high-performance new products.</description></item><item><title>AMP WEB</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/amp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/amp/</guid><description>Why is “Google Content Delivery Network Support (AMP)” getting so much attention? AMP is a standard jointly launched by Google and Twitter to make it easier for mobile users to view homepages. Direct translation of AMP (Accelerated Mobile Pages) means to speed up mobile pages.
In AMP, the search engine pre-reads the information on the page and directs the link from the search result to display the data without jumping to each page.</description></item><item><title>HUGO WEB</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/hugo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/hugo/</guid><description>Why is “Static Website Development” now attracting attention? There are three major reasons for operating a content management system (CMS) typified by Wordpress.
Security: Most CMSs are updated regularly. If the changes in the version upgrade are small, it will not cause a big problem, but if it is a major update, be careful. This may result in inconsistency with the installed plugins and extensions, which may lead to site malfunctions.</description></item><item><title>AZURE COSMOS DATABASE</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/database/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/database/</guid><description>Why is &amp;ldquo;database optimization&amp;rdquo; important? An increasing number of companies are using NOSQL to complement traditional RDBs to handle exponentially growing data, such as real-time analytics while holding large amounts of data.
So far we have used a database called RDBMS. The internal data structure was normalized, and it was necessary to refer to several master tables to display one screen.
A database called NOSQL, on the other hand, allows you to design the information you need in one shot.</description></item><item><title>AZURE TABLE STORAGE</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/storage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/solution/storage/</guid><description>Why is &amp;ldquo;Big Data&amp;rdquo; attracting attention? With the spread of smartphones, a large amount of data has started to appear. Even refrigerators and air conditioners are connected to the Internet and continue to generate new data. Corporate maintenance data is growing exponentially.
In the past, storage, storage, and processing of large-scale, diverse data have had issues of capacity, cost, speed, and so on. But with the advent of cheap table storage, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to store unnormalized data as raw information.</description></item></channel></rss>