<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Solution on Andaze Ltd.</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/</link><description>Recent content in Solution on Andaze Ltd.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andaze.com/en/solution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AZURE BOT FRAMEWORK</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/azure-bot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/azure-bot/</guid><description>AZURE BOT FRAMEWORK Chatbot Development&amp;quot; for 24-hour automated response to help increase customer satisfaction Overview A chatbot is an &amp;ldquo;automatic conversation system&amp;rdquo; that combines &amp;ldquo;chat&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;robot. They can reply to inquiries often received from users at internal help desks, customer support, etc., in place of staff using tools such as LINE. Andaze&amp;rsquo;s chatbot development is characterized by a high degree of accuracy that contributes to increased operational efficiency and customer satisfaction.</description></item><item><title>AZURE AI</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/azure-ai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/azure-ai/</guid><description>AZURE AI AI Machine Learning Development&amp;quot; for high prediction accuracy and improved business value Overview In recent years, with the spread of smartphones and IoT, a large amount of data has been accumulated. Analyzing this data by humans takes an enormous amount of time and effort. On the other hand, AI machine learning makes it possible to discover regularities that cannot be found by human power and to finish the analysis work in an instant.</description></item><item><title>Dynamics365</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/dynamics365/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/dynamics365/</guid><description>Dynamics365 Introduction of Customer Relationship Management CRM&amp;quot; for accurate analysis of information on existing customers for sales promotion. Overview CRM (Customer Relationship Management) is an IT tool that has been introduced in many successful companies. Now is the time when developing new customers is important, while correctly understanding existing customers and implementing the most appropriate strategy for each of them will pay off. Andaze helps you visualize the analysis of customer information with its superior solution Dynamics365 so that you can optimize your outreach to your users.</description></item><item><title>AZURE B2C</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/azure-b2c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/azure-b2c/</guid><description>AZURE B2C Superior Subject Authentication Service to Protect Sensitive Information from Hackers Overview Hacking and hijacking of applications can be a major social problem if personal information such as IDs and passwords are leaked to outside parties. AZURE B2C prevents data leakage and provides high security services. We work on system development while placing emphasis on the handling of personal information.
Effects of Introduction (1) Support millions of users and billions of authentications per day Securely handles billions of logins per day, preventing information leaks that could be fatal to the company.</description></item><item><title>BLAZOR WEB</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/blazor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/blazor/</guid><description>BLAZOR WEB SPA application development&amp;quot; that can provide comfortable web expression Overview SPA (Single Page Application) is a system in which contents are switched one after another on a single web page. The next content can be displayed without having to click on a link and reload the page. Andaze provides comfortable web expressions that run crisply, not to mention improved visuals and usability. This leads to increased user satisfaction.</description></item><item><title>SIGNALR</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/signalr/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/signalr/</guid><description>SIGNALR Interactive Communication Web Service Development&amp;quot; to make users&amp;rsquo; site browsing more comfortable Overview For example, real-time information, such as stock price charts and chats, is required as a product value. However, with conventional systems, information must be kept up-to-date through &amp;ldquo;periodic screen updates. This results in high communication volume, flickering screens, and other problems that can lead to a low level of user satisfaction.
Therefore, we recommend &amp;ldquo;interactive web services.</description></item><item><title>DEVEXPRESS</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/devexpress/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/devexpress/</guid><description>DEVEXPRESS UX-focused application development&amp;quot; that enhances the value of services through user satisfaction Overview Satisfaction and pleasure obtained through services and products. Such value that users experience and feel is called &amp;ldquo;UX (user experience). A decade ago, high functionality was enough to attract people&amp;rsquo;s interest and attention, but in recent years, when material wealth has been achieved, more and more people are willing to pay for &amp;ldquo;experience&amp;rdquo; in addition to functionality.</description></item><item><title>AMP WEB</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/amp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/amp/</guid><description>AMP WEB Mobile Content Acceleration&amp;quot; to reduce the waiting time until a web page is displayed Overview AMP (Accelerated Mobile Pages, commonly known as amp) is a standard jointly launched by Google and Twitter to enable mobile users to comfortably view websites. The literal translation means &amp;ldquo;faster pages for mobile.
AMP enables search engines to read information on web pages ahead of time and direct links from search results to them, so that data can be displayed without having to jump to the page each time.</description></item><item><title>HUGO WEB</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/hugo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/hugo/</guid><description>HUGO WEB Static Website Development for fast page loading with secure security Overview You want to increase the display speed of your web pages, or you want to have a solid security measure, or you do not want to update information in real time&amp;hellip;. Static website development is useful for websites with such characteristics. There are three main reasons why static websites are attracting attention today.
Effects of Introduction (1) Security Most CMS (Content Management System = a system that allows web content to be updated without specialized knowledge) are regularly upgraded.</description></item><item><title>AZURE COSMOS DATABASE</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/database/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/database/</guid><description>AZURE COSMOS DATABASE NOSQL Database Development&amp;quot; for storing huge databases with data optimization Overview Database file size is getting bigger and bigger. In order to handle exponentially increasing data, such as real-time analysis while maintaining such a large amount of data, &amp;ldquo;data optimization&amp;rdquo; is necessary. Therefore, an increasing number of companies are using NOSQL (abbreviation of Not only SQL) as a complement to the conventional RDB (Relational DataBase Management System / Relational DataBase Management System ).</description></item><item><title>AZURE TABLE STORAGE</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/storage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/storage/</guid><description>AZURE TABLE STORAGE Big Data Analytics Development&amp;quot; for inexpensive and speedy analysis of exponentially growing data Overview The recent proliferation of smartphones has led to the emergence of massive amounts of data. Moreover, even home appliances such as refrigerators, air conditioners, and vacuum cleaners are connected to the Internet and continue to generate new data. The amount of data held by companies is growing exponentially.
In order to store and process such large and varied data, problems of capacity, cost, and speed have been a constant concern until now.</description></item><item><title>Generic CRM for Customer Support</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/generic-crm-for-customer-support/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/generic-crm-for-customer-support/</guid><description>Generic CRM for Customer Support (in-house product) Providing smooth customer support for the omni-channel era This solution provides smooth customer support for customers accessing from various channels. It has a wide range of functions such as response history management, solution sharing, and document management. Customers can be served by operators via phone, chat, and SMS, as well as by AI-based virtual operators and chatbots that respond to customers in real time.</description></item><item><title>Generic CRM for Sales</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/generic-crm-for-sales/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/generic-crm-for-sales/</guid><description>Generic CRM for Sales (in-house product) Manage customer information and representative actions to support data-driven sales activities As the name &amp;ldquo;generic&amp;rdquo; suggests, Andaze&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Generic CRM&amp;rdquo; was developed as a generic version of CRM from the U.S. Generic CRM for Sales is a module to support sales activities by managing customer information and sales representatives&amp;rsquo; actions.
By preparing the system infrastructure necessary to improve customer engagement, which indicates the connection and trust between a company and its customers, we support efficient and effective sales activities based on data.</description></item><item><title>Workforce Analytics</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/solution/workforce-analytics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/solution/workforce-analytics/</guid><description>Workforce Analytics Workforce &amp;ldquo;Analysis&amp;rdquo; tool to increase productivity of companies promoting remote work. Andaze&amp;rsquo;s Occupancy Management System is a service platform as workforce analysis software that visualizes employee work performance, which is difficult to see due to remote work and other factors, and analyzes digital activity data to provide hints for improving work styles. With this tool, we will improve business processes and increase organizational and individual productivity and employee engagement* while uncovering issues and problems faced on a daily basis.</description></item></channel></rss>