<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365 on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/</link><description>Recent content in supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365 on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Let's learn about the basics of Dynamics 365.</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/dynamics365-basic-knowledge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/dynamics365-basic-knowledge/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the last issue, we wrote an article about accessing Dynamics 365 from the admin center.
If you are not an administrator, you can access the site from the following homepage.
https://home.dynamics.com
This will open the Dynamics 365 homepage.
In My Apps, you can see the available apps for the current user. So let&amp;rsquo;s double-click &amp;ldquo;Dynamics 365&amp;rdquo; in the following screen to access it.
Then, when you log in to Dynamics 365, you will see the following screen.</description></item><item><title>Let's take advantage of the sales functions of Dynamics 365.</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-sales-functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-sales-functions/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn So far, I have explained the features for administrators, but now I would like to introduce the features for sales and marketing.
First of all, in Dynamics 365 for sales, there are two default entities, one for sales and one for marketing. Depending on the stage of your business, the entities you use will differ depending on whether you are focusing on marketing activities to acquire potential customers or sales activities to potential customers to advance the sales process to a contract.</description></item><item><title>Let's try to use Dynamics 365 leads.</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-lead-entity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-lead-entity/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Now, we will use the Dynamics 365 sales entity while weaving in the previous scenario.
First, log in to Dynamics 365 and open Leads in the Sales area.
The following is a sample, but it shows the leads that are currently in progress (your open leads).
If you actually open one lead, you will see a screen like the one below. We will manage customer data, known as potential customers, in Leads.</description></item><item><title>Creating a Sales Case from a Lead in Dynamics 365</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/create-opportunity-from-lead/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/create-opportunity-from-lead/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous article, we talked about Leads in Dynamics 365. When a Lead becomes a Prospect, we will explain how to create a Client Company, a Client Representative, and a Sales Case from the Lead.
Assigning leads as potential. First, open a lead that you plan to discuss in the future. Then click on the &amp;ldquo;Prospect and Evaluate&amp;rdquo; button.
A duplicate check dialog will appear. If you already have a business relationship with a company and the contact person is the same, you can enter the company name and contact person name here.</description></item><item><title>Use Dynamics 365 activities to conduct business meetings.</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/p1036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/p1036/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous article, we created a sales case from a lead, and we need to keep track of the progress of the negotiation in the sales case. In this case, we can use an entity called activity.
Type of activity entity First, in Dynamics 365, there is an entity called Activity (Activity Pointer). These activities are associated with various entities such as client companies, contacts, sales projects, leads, support projects, etc.</description></item><item><title>Leverage Dynamics 365 trading partners and trading counterparts</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/utilize-account-and-contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/utilize-account-and-contact/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Now that I have told you about the sales projects and related activities, I will mention the parent entity, the client company and the client representative.
Relationships between client companies and upper and lower levels The client company, or company name, is the parent entity (higher-level entity) for client personnel, sales projects, and activities. In other words, based on the information of the client company, the information of the child entities (subordinate entities) is created and associated with it.</description></item><item><title>Use the email tracking feature</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/sales-insights-email-tracking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/sales-insights-email-tracking/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Dynamics 365 for Sales includes the ability to track opens, link clicks, and attachments to emails sent to customers, which is great because Salesforce requires you to purchase Pardot separately, but it&amp;rsquo;s available at no extra cost!
Reference Technical Information
Using Email Engagement to View Message Interactions
The setup is very simple, so I will summarize the steps.
Setting up an email profile Set up an email profile so that you can send emails in Dynamics.</description></item><item><title>Boost your sales force with Dynamics 365 product catalogs</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-catalog-for-sales/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-catalog-for-sales/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn So far, we have discussed how to manage sales deals that have been rated as &amp;ldquo;promising&amp;rdquo; by the lead.
In this article, I would like to explain how to manage the products that are important for sales projects on Dynamics 365.
The products that are important to the sales process are called product catalogs, and they allow you to manage what products are available (product families), in what units they are shipped (shipping unit list), and at what discount rates (discount and price lists) to generate quotes and invoices.</description></item><item><title>Create Dynamics 365 product families and bundles</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/product-family-bundle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/product-family-bundle/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous article, we created a single product and even a discount table. In this article, we will configure a product family and associate a product to the family. We will now discuss how to use product families.
Create a product family A product family is used to manage a group of similar products together. For example, there is a parent family of products called PCs, which can be divided into notebooks, desktops, and tablets as its child families.</description></item><item><title>Manage properties of Dynamics products</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/properties-of-product/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/properties-of-product/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn The following is a continuation of the previous article on product properties.
You can now create and use a complete Dynamics 365 product to price list. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at the products in more detail.
In the products that we offer, there are many different attributes and conditions. For example, in the case of cell phone cases, we need to classify the color, shape, size, available cell phone models, and condition (new or used).</description></item><item><title>Get the upper hand in negotiations with a Dynamics 365 discount table</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-discount-price-lists/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-discount-price-lists/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn With the product families we have created previously, we can now manage our sales case records more efficiently. Now, there will come a time when you need to adjust the final price of the deal. This is where the discount table comes into play.
We have already created a discount table in a previous article, so we will actually use this function.
Publish product families, products, and bundles The first step is to publish the product family, product, and bundle that you created in the previous article.</description></item><item><title>Leveraging cross-selling and up-selling of Dynamics 365 products</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-up-cross-sell-sales/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-up-cross-sell-sales/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In sales activities, up-selling and cross-selling are necessary activities to increase customer profitability.
Up-selling is a sales activity in which you sell your product or service as something higher and more expensive, while cross-selling is a sales activity in which you sell a combination of products and services related to the product or service you are selling.
In the properties of the online-only license, we had previously created that the segment was set up.</description></item><item><title>Manage everything from estimates to invoices with Dynamics 365</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/create-estimate-invoice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/create-estimate-invoice/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn So far, we have discussed sales projects and products in detail. If the business meeting goes well, we will prepare a quotation for the customer. If the quotation is accepted, the sales case is put in the &amp;ldquo;order&amp;rdquo; status, and an invoice is prepared and submitted to the customer.
I will now show you how to perform this process in Dynamics 365 for Sales.
Create a quote from a sales project.</description></item><item><title>Using Graphs in Dynamics 365</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-dynamics-graph/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-dynamics-graph/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn By using Dynamics 365 and continuing to effectively manage your sales activities, you will accumulate enough data in Dynamics 365 to consider your sales strategy.
You can use the data to help you determine what activities and sales talks are effective, research ways to approach different types of customers, and offer new products and services to win business.
What is even more remarkable is that Dynamics 365 allows you to process and visualize the data in reports, graphs, and dashboards based on the accumulated corporate data.</description></item><item><title>Managing Leads with Sales Funnels in Dynamics 365</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/manage-lead-by-sales-funnel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/manage-lead-by-sales-funnel/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In this article, I would like to talk about the &amp;ldquo;Sales Funnel&amp;rdquo;, which I mentioned in the section &amp;ldquo;Using Graphs in Dynamics 365&amp;rdquo;.
Let&amp;rsquo;s start by understanding what a sales funnel is, and then let&amp;rsquo;s actually create a sales funnel based on the data of potential customers called leads.
What is a sales funnel? Funnel means &amp;ldquo;funnel,&amp;rdquo; and is a device used for pouring liquid or powder into a container with a small diameter.</description></item><item><title>Managing Goals in Dynamics 365</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/create-sales-target-and-goal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/create-sales-target-and-goal/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In this article, we will talk about goals in Dynamics 365. In Dynamics 365, you can define goal indicators to manage your goals.
The following technical information is quoted as describing the function of goal management.
&amp;quot; The functions of goal management are as follows
Create a complex goal hierarchy. In this hierarchy, individual goal contributors or teams are assigned their own goals. Use goals in the hierarchy to track important business data (sales, customer service support cases, phone calls, etc.</description></item><item><title>Visualize information in the Dynamics 365 dashboard</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-dynamics-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-dynamics-dashboard/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn I have been informing you about the sales features of Dynamics 365. Now that you understand graphs, funnels, and goal management, let&amp;rsquo;s touch on dashboards.
There are two types of dashboards in Dynamics 365: system dashboards and user dashboards. The user dashboard allows you to visualize information by editing records that you have permissions for in graphs, grids, and lists.
In addition, system administrators can create system dashboards, which can be made public and configured for company-wide or departmental use.</description></item><item><title>Analyze data with Dynamics 365 reporting functions</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/analyze-data-by-reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/analyze-data-by-reports/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Dynamics 365 allows users to generate fetch-based reports using the Report Wizard. This feature can be used by users to collect and analyze data in a simplified manner.
How to create a report Creating a report is simple. First, click &amp;ldquo;Reports&amp;rdquo; from the menu.
Click the &amp;ldquo;+ New&amp;rdquo; button to create a new report.
Click &amp;ldquo;Report Wizard&amp;rdquo; to start creating a report.
If you want to create a new report, check the &amp;ldquo;Start a new report&amp;rdquo; box and click &amp;ldquo;Next&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Track the latest activity on your Dynamics 365 wall</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/trace-activities-by-wall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/trace-activities-by-wall/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn When I introduced the Dynamics 365 dashboard, I mentioned the wall.
In this article, I would like to post on the wall. when you open the Dynamics 365 home page, you will be taken to the default dashboard page, where the wall posts the status of each entity and allows you to track the active activities.
For example, when a new business partner company is created, when a competitor for a sales project is created, when an order is received or lost, etc.</description></item><item><title>Create a quote with Word template</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/create-quote-by-word-template/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/create-quote-by-word-template/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Here is a summary of the steps to create your own quote using the Word template.
advance preparation The first step is to create a sales case and add some products to be used in the quote. In this case, we added two products to the sales case and created a quote in advance with the tax amount added as well.
The total amount is as follows.</description></item></channel></rss>