<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dynamics-365-project-management on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/</link><description>Recent content in dynamics-365-project-management on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setting up the Project Service</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/setup-dynamics-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/setup-dynamics-project/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In this article, we will learn about Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation (Project Service), an application that can be used like Sales and Customer Service if you have purchased a Dynamics 365 Customer Engagement Plan license. If you have purchased a Dynamics 365 Customer Engagement Plan license, you can use this application in the same way as Sales and Customer Service, but Project Service is not as popular as Sales.</description></item><item><title>Create sales proposals from leads in Project Service</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/dynamics-psa-lead-to-opportunity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/dynamics-psa-lead-to-opportunity/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Now that we have completed the structure and configuration of Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation (PSA), let&amp;rsquo;s create a project and start managing it.
How to create a project As a review of the previous article, the process of creating a project involves the creation of company and contact information from the lead, as well as a sales case. If the quote created from the sales proposal is accepted, a project contract is created, and the project begins.</description></item><item><title>Create a project in the Project Service</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/dynamics-psa-create-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/dynamics-psa-create-project/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn This is a continuation of the previous article, where we created a sales case from a lead in Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation (Project Service), and now we are going to create a project.
Create estimates from sales projects After a series of negotiations with prospective customers, we have entered the last quotation phase in the negotiations. The quotation is created within the sales project. This is the same as in the case of Sales.</description></item><item><title>Plan your project with Project Service</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/plan-project-schedule-resource/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/plan-project-schedule-resource/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Now that we have completed the creation of the previous project, let&amp;rsquo;s fill in the contents of the project. When a project starts, a project plan is generally prepared with the following structure.
Project Objectives and Goals Scope (range) Schedule Cost System (Resources) Communication Quality Management Lists and countermeasures Reference: Can a PM beginner do it? How to make a project plan
In this article, we will use the WBS and Schedule Board of Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation.</description></item><item><title>Project Service Manage and close projects</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/manage-and-close-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/manage-and-close-project/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In this article, you will learn how to plan a project in Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation. Once the plan is made, the project will be started. In this section, we will introduce the steps to manage a project.
Estimated cost management After the project members are selected from the resources and assigned to each WBS, the estimated labor cost is automatically calculated according to the WBS.</description></item><item><title>Project Service resource allocation and shipping units</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/psa-assign-team-members/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/psa-assign-team-members/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn When you create a project in Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation and assign team members, the calculation of the assigned time for the assigned members is a bit complicated, so I will show you how it works.
Resource &amp;ldquo;allocation method&amp;rdquo;. When you assign resources as a team member of a project, you have a choice in the field called &amp;ldquo;Assignment Method&amp;rdquo;.
If you check the official page, you will see that it means the following.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshoot PSA Schedule Board</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/psa-troubleshoot-schedule-board/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/psa-troubleshoot-schedule-board/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn As I mentioned when I planned a project in Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation (PSA), Project Service seems to behave differently depending on the interface and version differences.
It may be possible to improve this by upgrading the version, but here are the steps we took to deal with it in version 2 first.
*This will be available as of January 2019.
Background: Moving to a unified interface The menu that you are used to in version 8 of Dynamics 365 is called the Web Interface, but in version 9, a new interface called the Unified Interface has been added that is also mobile friendly.</description></item><item><title>Editing WBS in Project Service and Microsoft Project</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/editing-wbs-by-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/editing-wbs-by-project/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn By integrating Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation with Microsoft Project, you can edit WBS on a client terminal. In this article, we will show you how to integrate them.
*This article assumes that you already have Microsoft Project installed on your device. If you have not installed it yet, please install it from the Microsoft 365 Management Center as shown below.
Install Microsoft Project If you have an Office 365 subscription, you can install Microsoft Project from Office 365.</description></item><item><title>Update the Project Service working template</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/psa-update-work-template/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/psa-update-work-template/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn This section provides instructions on how to update a work template in Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation.In the previous section, &amp;ldquo;Planning a Project with Project Service&amp;rdquo;, we showed you how to create a work template, but this is the procedure to follow if you want to change the holidays, operating hours, etc. of a work template that has already been set up.
How to update the working template After setting up the work templates you have already created for your resources and projects, you may need to update them by adding holidays or changing the operating hours due to various factors.</description></item></channel></rss>