<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sustainability on Andaze Ltd.</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/</link><description>Recent content in Sustainability on Andaze Ltd.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 08:33:31 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Top Message</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/message/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:02:12 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/message/</guid><description>Top Message Andaze was founded in 2016. The impetus for the company's founding came from my trip to India in 2011. What I experienced there, what I felt firsthand, and what I wondered about.... As a result of my search for what I could do and the pursuit of my ideals, Andaze was born. In recent years, sustainability has been positioned as an important factor in management strategy, and we have been working to provide our employees, who come from a variety of backgrounds including nationalities, with a diverse and personalized work style that allows them to work fully remotely, and to accelerate the business value generated from this work style.</description></item><item><title>Human Rights Policy</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/human-rights/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:02:12 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/human-rights/</guid><description>Human Rights Policy Andaze&amp;rsquo;s management philosophy is &amp;ldquo;Bringing innovation to Japan through global and superior technology. Andaze&amp;rsquo;s management philosophy is to &amp;ldquo;Bring innovation to Japan through global and superior technology. Based on this philosophy, we will make company-wide efforts to respect the human rights of all people involved in our business activities. Respect for International Human Rights Norms We understand and respect as a minimum the human rights described in the International Bill of Human Rights, including the Universal Declaration of Human Rights, and the core labor standards of the International Labor Organization (ILO) Declaration on Fundamental Principles and Rights at Work.</description></item><item><title>Environmental Policy</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/environmental-policy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:02:12 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/environmental-policy/</guid><description>Environmental Policy We at Andaze have established the following Environmental Policy as a guideline to fulfill our responsibility toward the realization of a sustainable society. Resource Recycling Initiatives In order to shift from a consumption-oriented to a recycling-oriented economy and to pass on a sustainable global environment to future generations, we will promote initiatives to effectively utilize resources throughout the entire process from procurement to use and disposal of products and systems.</description></item><item><title>Effective use of resources</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/resources/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:02:12 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/resources/</guid><description>Effective use of resources We at Andaze believe that it is important for people living on the earth to address environmental issues such as climate change. We are working to reduce our environmental impact with the aim of achieving a sustainable society. Promoting a paperless work environment We are eliminating conventional paper-based meetings and distribution of materials to the greatest extent possible. We place emphasis on digital meetings using monitors and other devices both inside and outside the company.</description></item><item><title>Contribution to society based on our corporate philosophy</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/contribution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:02:12 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/contribution/</guid><description>Contribution to society based on our corporate philosophy Andaze is committed to &amp;ldquo;Bringing innovation to Japan through global and superior technology. We at Andaze are committed to promoting sustainable initiatives for our business partners, the people we serve, and society as a whole based on our corporate philosophy of &amp;ldquo;Bringing Innovation to Japan through Global Excellence. Diversity and Inclusion We value human resources above all else. There is no discrimination or distinction.</description></item><item><title>Information Security Management System</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/information-security-management/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:02:12 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/information-security-management/</guid><description>Information Security Management System We at Andaze recognize that ensuring the security of our customers&amp;rsquo; information and personal information is a top management priority. Andaze has obtained ISO 27001 certification, the international standard for information security management systems (ISMS), to ensure the security management, confidentiality, integrity, and availability of information.</description></item><item><title>Basic Policy on Information Security</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/information-security-policy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:02:12 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/sustainability/information-security-policy/</guid><description>Basic Policy on Information Security Andaze is committed to ensuring, maintaining, and utilizing information security, one of the most important issues in our business activities, in accordance with our corporate philosophy of &amp;ldquo;Bringing innovation to Japan through global and superior technology. We, Andaze Corporation, have established and implemented the following Basic Policy on Information Security based on our belief that it is our responsibility to protect all information assets we handle in order to ensure, maintain, and utilize information security, which is one of the most important issues in our business activities.</description></item></channel></rss>