<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Company on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/company/</link><description>Recent content in Company on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/company/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Top Message</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/company/message/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/company/message/</guid><description>Top Message As a true technology supporter who also understands business strategy, we contribute to transformation through the use of digital technology. Andaze is a leading company in the field of technology development and consulting. Andaze is a venture company born from the spin-out of professionals active on the front lines of various fields Andaze is a venture company created through the spin-out of leading professionals in various fields, from technology development to consulting.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/company/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/company/about/</guid><description>About Us What is Andaze ? Leveraging IT Tech from Around the World We create the best products by communicating with users. and communicate with users to create the best products. We are a next-generation development company that creates optimal products by communicating with users.
Andaze creates products that change common sense. &amp;ldquo;Andaze&amp;rdquo;, which creates products that change the way we think about the world.
About Us Company Name: Andaze Corporation</description></item><item><title>History</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/company/history/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/company/history/</guid><description>History · 2011 Representative Arai came to India
· 2015 Returned from India. Started preparing to establish a company.
· 2016 Founding of Andaze Co.
· 2017 Microsoft Network Partner Certification
· Certified as a Microsoft Silver Partner in 2018
· 2019 Head office relocated from Toranomon to Kojimachi
· 2019 Capital Increase (5 million → 10 million)
· 2020 Establish development base at WeWork Hanzomon
· 2020 Microsoft Gold Partner Certification</description></item><item><title>Management Philosophy</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/company/philosophy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/company/philosophy/</guid><description>Management Philosophy Supporting corporate DX at the forefront of technology. In this day and age, it is impossible to compete only on the quality and price of products. To survive in the competitive marketplace of the future, you need DX to drive business value at an accelerated rate. Andaze is a company that adds value to businesses and And we contribute to the creation of innovative innovations that fundamentally overturn existing business models.</description></item></channel></rss>