<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Company on Andaze Ltd.</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/company/</link><description>Recent content in Company on Andaze Ltd.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andaze.com/en/company/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Top Message</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/company/message/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/company/message/</guid><description>Top Message As a true technology supporter who also understands business strategy, we contribute to transformation through the use of digital technology.
Andaze is a venture company created by spin-outs of leading professionals in various fields ranging from technology development to consulting.
Since its inception, Andaze has always been on the lookout for trends and has been generous in its use of superior technology.
All members of the team are highly motivated and function as players in the industry.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/company/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/company/about/</guid><description>About Us Company Name Andaze Ltd. Location [Head office]
10-3, Kojimachi 2-chome, Chiyoda-ku, Tokyo
[Development base]
WeWork Hanzomon PREXSouth, 5-1, Kojimachi 2-chome, Chiyoda-ku, Tokyo
Established April 2016, Fiscal year March Capital 20,000,000 Yen Representative Mina Arai Bank Sumitomo Mitsui Banking Corporation, Hibiya Branch The Japan Net Bank, Limited, Head Office Sales Department Approved Standards Information Security Management System (ISO27001) Quality Management System (ISO9001) Phone number 03-3230-0401 Website https://andaze.com Business Diagnosis, guidance, and consulting of management information systems for various companies Consulting on business improvement and IT strategy Investment in information and telecommunications businesses and consulting on mergers, alliances, and transfers of business rights of these companies Planning, development, import and export of computer software Production and sale of publications and electronic content Consulting and advertising agency services related to employee recruitment for various companies Development of personnel systems and educational programs, and planning and implementation of education and training Buying, selling, holding and managing securities Investment advisory services related to securities, and all businesses incidental and related to the above</description></item><item><title>History</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/company/history/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/company/history/</guid><description>History 2011 Representative Arai came to India 2015 Returned from India. Started preparing to establish a company 2016 Founding of Andaze Ltd. 2018 Certified as a Microsoft Silver Partner 2019 Head office relocated from Toranomon to Kojimachi 2019 Capital Increase to 10 million yen 2020 Establish development base at WeWork Hanzomon 2020 Certified as a Microsoft Gold Partner 2021 Obtained ISO 9001 and ISO 27001 certification 2021 Capital Increase to 20 million yen</description></item><item><title>Management Philosophy</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/company/philosophy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/company/philosophy/</guid><description>Management Philosophy Supporting corporate DX at the forefront of technology. In this era, it is no longer possible to compete only on product quality and price.
What is needed to survive in the competitive market of the future is DX,
which drives business value at an accelerated pace.
Andaze contributes to the creation of innovative innovations
that add value to businesses and overturn existing business models.
Professionals with diverse skills create new added value</description></item></channel></rss>