<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Service archive on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/services/</link><description>Recent content in Service archive on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AI（Artificial Intelligence）</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/services/ai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/services/ai/</guid><description>AI (Artificial Intelligence) Providing highly accurate AI solutions that further enhance business value
Andaz&amp;rsquo;s AI solutions, based on our strength of abundant knowledge and advanced technology, are highly accurate and contribute significantly to business efficiency. Our shared team, which is involved from consulting to development and operation, achieves high-level AI development. We further enhance the quality of our solutions by repeatedly improving them through design illustrations and prototypes that are easy to visualize.</description></item><item><title>クラウド</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/services/cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/services/cloud/</guid><description>Cloud Computing　 Supporting the Best Cloud Deployment for Your Digital Strategy Cloud computing is essential for DX. In addition, the adoption of the most appropriate cloud service is required depending on the customer&amp;rsquo;s business challenges and system environment. Andaz will develop a detailed migration roadmap in accordance with the customer&amp;rsquo;s industry, company size, and requirements. We not only realize the migration of existing systems to the cloud, but also provide access to them under safer and more secure security, which will be a driving force to promote the transformation of your company in the wake of digitalization.</description></item><item><title>コンサルティング</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/services/consulting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/services/consulting/</guid><description>Consulting　 Experienced consultants with a high level of expertise
DX enables our clients to transform all aspects of their corporate activities for the better. Andaz&amp;rsquo;s shared team of highly specialized digital consultants provides a comprehensive range of services, from strategy development and implementation to customer support, to help you design a digital strategy that works for you.
Why choose Andaz?　 (1) We understand your business challenges and needs, and create effective solutions.</description></item><item><title>UI/UXデザイン</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/services/design/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/services/design/</guid><description>UI/UX Design Supporting the development of products that are comfortable, pleasant, and easy to use
Beautiful design, easy-to-use functions, and intuitive colors and tastes. Andaz expresses UI and UX in the best possible way based on our extensive experience and knowledge. We leverage our high level of expertise to support development that places the highest priority on the customer experience while adhering to the client&amp;rsquo;s requirements. Experience the best UI/UX design with meaning and value in every single piece.</description></item><item><title>Recruitment agency services</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/services/recruit-agency/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/services/recruit-agency/</guid><description>Recruitment Agency Services Total support from recruiting to hiring and training
Andaz utilizes AI to select the most effective media and methods among diversifying recruitment methods. We also provide a series of HR services on behalf of our clients, from consulting to recruitment planning, job posting, scheduling, and post-hire training, etc. We support strategic recruitment activities by analyzing market trends and information obtained through our professional knowledge cultivated by supporting more than 200 companies in their recruitment, and through collaboration with various agencies and partner companies.</description></item><item><title>新規事業サービス開発</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/services/service-develop/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/services/service-develop/</guid><description>New Business Service Development　 Support from new business to expansion using existing systems
From the digitization of analog information such as documents to new businesses that create business models from scratch, the possibilities for DX are endless. Andaz&amp;rsquo;s one-stop shared team with over 20 years of experience handles everything from strategic planning to implementation, operation, and maintenance of services utilizing superior technology. More objective and neutral. We support your digital innovation within the feasible cost range.</description></item><item><title>シェアードチーム</title><link>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/services/shared/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.github.io/WebCorporate/en/services/shared/</guid><description>Shared Team Why Choose Andaz? Andaz professionals Shared Teams&amp;quot; (move from the services we provide) to support the success of your project. A diverse team of highly skilled professionals
Shared Team is a group of professionals from various fields. Each consultant, PM, and engineer takes the initiative in steering the project to achieve the goals. By not having a fixed number of team members, all Andaz staff naturally understand the client&amp;rsquo;s technical information, regardless of the size of the project.</description></item></channel></rss>