<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Service on Andaze Ltd.</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/</link><description>Recent content in Service on Andaze Ltd.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andaze.com/en/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AI（Artificial Intelligence）</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/artificial-intelligence/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/services/artificial-intelligence/</guid><description>AI (Artificial Intelligence) Development Services Providing highly accurate AI solutions that help solve problems and realize business strategies With the spread of the Internet of Things (IoT), it is now commonplace to analyze the vast and diverse data acquired from sensors and utilize it for business purposes. By combining big data and AI, it is possible to discover the hidden needs of consumers and create new business opportunities, or to improve operations at production sites to improve product quality and reduce costs.</description></item><item><title>Cloud</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/services/cloud/</guid><description>Support services for de-subscription, de-clouding, and de-packaging Support for &amp;ldquo;de-subscription, de-cloud, and de-packaging&amp;rdquo; in terms of cost, security, and system operation Cloud services (SaaS), which have become indispensable for businesses, offer a variety of advantages, such as improved efficiency in operations and management. In addition, companies are moving away from SaaS, moving away from cloud computing, and moving away from package services. Furthermore, due to the limitations of system operations, an increasing number of companies are re-evaluating the advantages of their in-house &amp;ldquo;on-premise&amp;rdquo; systems and viewing their operations in a positive light.</description></item><item><title>Consulting</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/consulting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/services/consulting/</guid><description>PoC (Proof of Concept)
Prototyping and Prototyping Services We provide &amp;ldquo;prototyping, implementation, and verification&amp;rdquo; to confirm the feasibility of system development and make investment decisions. The first step to successful DX is PoC, which stands for &amp;ldquo;Proof of Concept&amp;rdquo;, to find the feasibility of system development, to actually conduct small-scale prototyping and implementation, and to verify the results with the finished product in order to make a decision on whether or not to make an IT investment.</description></item><item><title>Static Site Generator</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/design/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/services/design/</guid><description>Static website building service (website acceleration) &amp;ldquo;Static website development&amp;rdquo; to speed up website display and enhance security. We often hear from corporate marketers that &amp;ldquo;even if we spend a large amount of money on advertising to drive visitors from SNS and LPs to our website, the slow website display speed results in high direct return and abandonment rates, and our conversion rate is not increasing. In fact, a global online sales company has analyzed that &amp;ldquo;a 0.</description></item><item><title>Recruitment agency services</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/recruit-agency/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/services/recruit-agency/</guid><description>Recruitment Agency Services Total support from recruiting to hiring and training Andaze utilizes AI to select the most effective media and methods among diversifying recruitment methods. We also provide a series of HR services on behalf of our clients, from consulting to recruitment planning, job posting, scheduling, and post-hire training, etc. We support strategic recruitment activities by analyzing market trends and information obtained through our professional knowledge cultivated by supporting more than 200 companies in their recruitment, and through collaboration with various agencies and partner companies.</description></item><item><title>New Business Service Development</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/service-develop/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/services/service-develop/</guid><description>New Business System Development Services (SaaS Development) Flexible and speedy system development that leads new businesses to success. A new business is a project with a large &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t know until you try it&amp;rdquo; element. If the system is developed using the waterfall method, in which all necessary functions are determined in the initial requirements definition before proceeding with development, rework will occur every time a modification to the requirements or design occurs, costing a great deal of time and money.</description></item><item><title>Workforce Analytics</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/shared/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:03:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/services/shared/</guid><description>Remote Time and Attendance Service Monitoring attendance and productivity while protecting the privacy of remote employees The spread of the new coronavirus outbreak has prompted an increasing number of companies to allow their employees to work remotely. Even now that the outbreak has subsided, the trend toward allowing various work styles without requiring employees to work in the office is accelerating. On the other hand, many executives and managers say, &amp;ldquo;I trust my employees and subordinates, but I don&amp;rsquo;t know how they work remotely,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;I am worried about the risk of compliance violations.</description></item><item><title>IoT/Big Data Development Services</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/iot-big/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/services/iot-big/</guid><description>IoT/Big Data Development Services Supporting data utilization that leads to business innovation and new business opportunities With the promotion of DX, an increasing number of companies are seeking to &amp;ldquo;successfully link the large amount of data (Big Data) they possess to their business&amp;rdquo;. This data is useful in understanding the current situation and making accurate judgments based on it, without relying on human experience and intuition. By referring to predictive analysis of big data and linking it to operational reforms and the creation of new businesses, we will realize the establishment of DX and a shift to &amp;ldquo;data-driven management,&amp;rdquo; in which management is conducted while making use of data.</description></item><item><title>IoT/Big Data Development Services</title><link>https://andaze.com/en/services/iot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/en/services/iot/</guid><description>IoT/Big Data Development Services Supporting data utilization that leads to business innovation and new business opportunities With the promotion of DX, an increasing number of companies are seeking to &amp;ldquo;successfully link the large amount of data (Big Data) they possess to their business&amp;rdquo;. This data is useful in understanding the current situation and making accurate judgments based on it, without relying on human experience and intuition. By referring to predictive analysis of big data and linking it to operational reforms and the creation of new businesses, we will realize the establishment of DX and a shift to &amp;ldquo;data-driven management,&amp;rdquo; in which management is conducted while making use of data.</description></item></channel></rss>