<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dynamics-365-customization on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/</link><description>Recent content in dynamics-365-customization on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Try to embed Javascript code in Dynamics 365</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/d365-usage-js-onform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/d365-usage-js-onform/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Forms in Dynamics 365 allow you to insert web resources, which allow you to add HTML, Javascript, image files and Silverlight applications, giving you relative flexibility in customizing your forms.
Customer Engagement Web Resources
This time, we will embed a Javascript code in the form and if the &amp;ldquo;Phone&amp;rdquo; field is blank, we will make the &amp;ldquo;Fax&amp;rdquo; field read-only. Something as simple as this could be done quickly by business rules, but this time we&amp;rsquo;ll do it as a test.</description></item><item><title>Set XRM ToolBox to hide the sitemap</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/hide-setting-sitemap-by-xrmtoolbox/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/hide-setting-sitemap-by-xrmtoolbox/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In this article, I will show you how to use a third party customization tool called XRM ToolBox to make the &amp;ldquo;Settings&amp;rdquo; sitemap visible only to users with administrative privileges.
Important note: XRM ToolBox is a Dynamics development tool that is introduced in the Japan Microsoft Dynamics 365 Team Blog. If you wish to use it, please do so at your own risk after thorough verification. Please note that we are not responsible for any damages caused by the contents of this site.</description></item><item><title>Launching a Process in a Dynamics 365 Batch</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/use-batch-process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/use-batch-process/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In this case, we&amp;rsquo;re using a solution from Microsoft Labs. This section describes how to execute Dynamics 365 workflows in batch processing at a specified time.
Important note: If you wish to use the Change Tracking Solution in your own environment, please do so at your own risk after thorough verification. Please note that we cannot be held responsible for any damages caused by the contents of this website.</description></item><item><title>Dynamics 365 Extensions - Workflow Tools</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/dynamics-solution-workflow-tools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/dynamics-solution-workflow-tools/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn I would like to introduce you to Dynamics 365 Workflow Tools, which greatly extends the functionality of Dynamics 365 Workflow. This is a great way to use the solution that I previously recommended in What is the best third party solution?
Important note: Dynamics 365 Workflow Tools is a third party solution. If you wish to use them in your own environment, please verify them thoroughly and use them at your own risk.</description></item><item><title>Exporting Dynamics 365 data to Azure SQL</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/exporting-d365data-to-azuresql/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/exporting-d365data-to-azuresql/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn We will show you how to export Dynamics 365 data to Azure SQL Server using an add-on service called Data Export Service.
Although Dynamics 365 provides data recovery by tracking data changes through audit history and restoring instances through date/time backups, there was no convenient way to restore deleted data other than using XRM Toolbox, so the Data Export Service is very useful.
The procedure for setting up the Data Export Service is described in the official document Replicating Data in an Azure SQL Database, but the procedure for generating the Key Vault URL was not done correctly by reading the document alone, so I decided to summarize it this time by adding the contents of my research.</description></item><item><title>Ribbon Workbench: Show and Hide Buttons by Field Value</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/ribbon-workbench-hide-button-with-field-value/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/ribbon-workbench-hide-button-with-field-value/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn You can use Ribbon Workbench to show or hide the buttons.
However, if you simply want to hide unnecessary buttons, you can do so by adjusting the permissions in the security role.
So this time, we will add a setting to show or hide the field depending on its value.
advance preparation Before doing any customization, do some advance preparation.
Importing Ribbon Workbench Ribbon Workbench can be downloaded from RIBBON WORKBENCH.</description></item></channel></rss>