<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cooperation-with-other-systems on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/</link><description>Recent content in cooperation-with-other-systems on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Save the Dynamics 365 document to SharePoint</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/use-sharepoint-saving-docs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/use-sharepoint-saving-docs/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Dynamics 365 provides storage space based on the number of licenses. If you use the trial version of Dynamics 365, you will only have about 5GB of storage space, so if you upload attachments to your business partners&amp;rsquo; records, you will quickly run out of storage space.
Therefore, in Dynamics 365, by linking with SharePoint Online, you can change the destination of the actual file from Dynamics 365 to SharePoint Online.</description></item><item><title>Linking Dynamics 365 and Yammer for interactive information exchange</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/dynamics365-with-yammer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/dynamics365-with-yammer/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn One of the features of Dynamics 365 for external system integration is the integration with Yammer; if you are using Yammer internally, you can use it with Dynamics 365 to actively exchange information about customers and business meetings internally.
What is Yammer? Yammer is, simply put, an internal social network. By setting access rights by company organizational unit, information can be exchanged securely. It can also be linked to SharePoint, so it is possible to share documents and minutes used in meetings across related departments within the company.</description></item><item><title>Integrate Dynamics 365 and Power Bi to enhance dashboards</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/create-powerbi-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/create-powerbi-dashboard/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Dynamics 365 has an existing dashboard function, but if you integrate Power BI, you will be able to check information more graphically.
Power BI is a business intelligence tool provided by Microsoft. It is a tool that processes large amounts of data and provides visualized information that is effective for business.
For more information, see What is Power BI? for more information. Also, Power BI Pro is available as a free trial version, so please take advantage of it.</description></item><item><title>Retrieve data from on-premises SQL Server</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/getting-data-from-on-premise-sql/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/getting-data-from-on-premise-sql/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Dynamics 365 can be integrated with PowerApps, Flow, and Power BI, called Power Platform, to further enhance its value. If you have a Dynamics 365 Customer Engagement Plan license, you should definitely take advantage of this application.
Currently, Dynamics 365 uses the Common Data Service to manage data, so data stored in Dynamics 365 can be seamlessly passed to PowerApps, Flow, and Power BI, which also use the Common Data Service.</description></item><item><title>Using Dynamics 365 for Outlook</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/dynamics365-app-for-outlook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/dynamics365-app-for-outlook/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn One of the most useful features of Dynamics 365 is its integration with Outlook.
If you are an Outlook user, you can check your Dynamics customer and case information and update your activity information directly from Outlook.
You can also update your activity information, so if you are already using Office 365, there is no reason not to use it.
There are some things you need to do to use Dynamics 365 for Outlook.</description></item></channel></rss>