<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>initial-setup-of-dynamics-365 on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/</link><description>Recent content in initial-setup-of-dynamics-365 on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Add a Dynamics 365 user</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/adding-user/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/adding-user/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Once you have created a tenant instance of Dynamics 365, here are the steps to add users to Dynamics 365. Since Dynamics 365 synchronizes user information with Office 365, you will basically be updating user information in Office 365.
Adding users in Office 365 First, log in to the Office 365 (or Microsoft 365 as of January 2019) Management Center. From the left panel, open &amp;ldquo;Users&amp;rdquo;, click &amp;ldquo;Active Users&amp;rdquo;, and then click &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Dynamics 365 Security Basic Settings</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/basic-security-settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/basic-security-settings/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Now that we have added a user in Dynamics 365, let&amp;rsquo;s understand the basic security structure and settings. Dynamics 365 has the following security structure.
Departments and teams are groups of organizations, and you can manage organization groups in detail by adding users within them. Security Roles and Field Security are used to control access rights. *In this section, we will introduce them. Field security will be introduced in another article.</description></item><item><title>Importing data into Dynamics 365</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/how-to-import-data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/how-to-import-data/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Once you have Dynamics 365 set up, it is time to import data. There are several ways to import data, but this article will discuss how to prepare the imported data and perform the import process.
Preparing for Data Import First, there are two ways to import data in Dynamics 365.
The first is to import using an Excel template for import. The other way is to import the data in Excel Online.</description></item><item><title>Configure Dynamics 365 Field Security</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/set-security-field-profile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/set-security-field-profile/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn We have talked about security in terms of roles, departments, and teams. I think it&amp;rsquo;s safe to say that this knowledge is enough to set up security in your company.
However, what if more detailed security settings are required in the process of operating the system? For example, even within the same department, there are situations where detailed security settings are required, such as hiding or prohibiting the writing of information in each field.</description></item><item><title>About Dynamics 365 Hierarchical Security Settings</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/use-security-hierarchy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/use-security-hierarchy/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In addition to security roles that control security on a per-entity basis, field security on a per-field basis, and department and team security for managing user affiliations, Dynamics 365 has an evolving security concept called hierarchical security.
Hierarchical security settings are not enabled by default, but the steps we will show you will allow you to configure them.
What you can do with hierarchical security With hierarchical security, even if a user&amp;rsquo;s access privileges to an entity are set to &amp;ldquo;user only&amp;rdquo; (can only access their own records), they can still view and edit the data of users below them in the hierarchy, which is a big advantage of keeping the security role settings simple and expanding the access range.</description></item><item><title>Using the Dynamics 365 Portal Add-on</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/use-dynamics-portal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/use-dynamics-portal/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn The Dynamics 365 Customer Engagement Plan application comes standard with one portal add-on.
The advantages of using a portal include the following
Provide services and information using Dynamics 365 data to users outside the organization who do not have a license to use Dynamics 365. Web services can be easily built by simply creating and editing Dynamics 365 records. You can easily build web services by simply creating and editing Dynamics 365 records.</description></item><item><title>Configuring Dynamics 365 Apps</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/dynamics-setting-application/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/dynamics-setting-application/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In this section, we will talk a little bit about Dynamics 365 applications.
In Dynamics 365, a new feature called &amp;ldquo;Applications&amp;rdquo; is available, which allows users to set access permissions based on their security roles.
Right after the installation of Dynamics 365, default applications, sales, services, etc. are created. For example, you can manage the sales force in your company by giving them access to an application called Sales, so that they do not see unnecessary entities or data in advance.</description></item><item><title>How to deal with Dynamics 365 import errors</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/dynamics-import-error/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/dynamics-import-error/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous article, we have shown you how to import data using Excel template, but if an error occurs during data import, what should you do?
When do I get an error? First of all, the most common error in the template is due to duplicate data, as you can see in the Excel template, the value of the reference field is entered based on the display name.</description></item><item><title>Data import in Dynamics 365 Excel Online</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/import-data-from-excel-online/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/import-data-from-excel-online/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous article, we introduced the process of importing data using an import template. This method can be very useful when importing initial data. In this article, I will describe how to import data dynamically in Excel Online based on the view you have created instead of using a template.
Note that you do not need to have Excel client installed on your local PC to edit dynamically in Excel Online.</description></item></channel></rss>