<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dynamics 365 Blog on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/</link><description>Recent content in Dynamics 365 Blog on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 15:53:27 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Dynamics 365 licensing costs</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/implementing-dynamics-365/type-license-dynamics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/implementing-dynamics-365/type-license-dynamics/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous chapter, we have discussed the uses, functions, and usage scenarios of Dynamics 365. It is a highly functional product with seamless integration with existing Microsoft products. However, the appeal of Dynamics 365 is not only in its features.
How much is the basic cost of a Dynamics 365 license? In this section, we will introduce the cost of Dynamics 365 licenses in comparison with other CRM systems.</description></item><item><title>Add a Dynamics 365 user</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/adding-user/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/adding-user/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Once you have created a tenant instance of Dynamics 365, here are the steps to add users to Dynamics 365. Since Dynamics 365 synchronizes user information with Office 365, you will basically be updating user information in Office 365.
Adding users in Office 365 First, log in to the Office 365 (or Microsoft 365 as of January 2019) Management Center. From the left panel, open &amp;ldquo;Users&amp;rdquo;, click &amp;ldquo;Active Users&amp;rdquo;, and then click &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Dynamics 365 Instance NORMALITY</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/normality-of-instance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/normality-of-instance/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn We have been managing instances of Dynamics 365 by operating the Management Center. Now we will introduce how to manage the instances to make sure they are working properly.
Checking Instance Integrity To check the normality of the instance, open Service Normality. If the Normalcy column is set to &amp;ldquo;Normal Service&amp;rdquo;, then the instance is normal.
Check the storage area of the instance You can also check the storage space to be used.</description></item><item><title>Let's learn about the basics of Dynamics 365.</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/dynamics365-basic-knowledge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/dynamics365-basic-knowledge/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the last issue, we wrote an article about accessing Dynamics 365 from the admin center.
If you are not an administrator, you can access the site from the following homepage.
https://home.dynamics.com
This will open the Dynamics 365 homepage.
In My Apps, you can see the available apps for the current user. So let&amp;rsquo;s double-click &amp;ldquo;Dynamics 365&amp;rdquo; in the following screen to access it.
Then, when you log in to Dynamics 365, you will see the following screen.</description></item><item><title>Save the Dynamics 365 document to SharePoint</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/use-sharepoint-saving-docs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/use-sharepoint-saving-docs/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Dynamics 365 provides storage space based on the number of licenses. If you use the trial version of Dynamics 365, you will only have about 5GB of storage space, so if you upload attachments to your business partners&amp;rsquo; records, you will quickly run out of storage space.
Therefore, in Dynamics 365, by linking with SharePoint Online, you can change the destination of the actual file from Dynamics 365 to SharePoint Online.</description></item><item><title>Setting up Dynamics 365 for Marketing</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/marketing-with-dynamics-365/dynamics-365-for-marketing-setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/marketing-with-dynamics-365/dynamics-365-for-marketing-setup/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Have you ever heard of a marketing support application called Dynamics 365 for Marketing?
Dynamics 365 for Marketing is an application that allows you to analyze how effective your marketing efforts are in reaching potential customers who have received information from your company&amp;rsquo;s website, blog, mail magazines, or who have attended your seminars or events.
Originally, Marketing was a marketing function associated with Sales that could be used mainly for sending campaign emails.</description></item><item><title>Setting up the Project Service</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/setup-dynamics-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/setup-dynamics-project/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In this article, we will learn about Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation (Project Service), an application that can be used like Sales and Customer Service if you have purchased a Dynamics 365 Customer Engagement Plan license. If you have purchased a Dynamics 365 Customer Engagement Plan license, you can use this application in the same way as Sales and Customer Service, but Project Service is not as popular as Sales.</description></item><item><title>Try to embed Javascript code in Dynamics 365</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/d365-usage-js-onform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/d365-usage-js-onform/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Forms in Dynamics 365 allow you to insert web resources, which allow you to add HTML, Javascript, image files and Silverlight applications, giving you relative flexibility in customizing your forms.
Customer Engagement Web Resources
This time, we will embed a Javascript code in the form and if the &amp;ldquo;Phone&amp;rdquo; field is blank, we will make the &amp;ldquo;Fax&amp;rdquo; field read-only. Something as simple as this could be done quickly by business rules, but this time we&amp;rsquo;ll do it as a test.</description></item><item><title>Understand the CRM system</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/understanding-dynamics-365/crm-system/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/understanding-dynamics-365/crm-system/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Have you ever heard of Dynamics 365 provided by Microsoft? Microsoft Dynamics 365 is a business application that integrates and utilizes data from various departments such as sales, marketing, accounting, general affairs, and human resources into a single application.
It used to be divided into Dynamics CRM, a product for sales, service, and marketing that required customer relationship management, and ERP (accounting, supply chain, project, and human resource management) products called Dynamics AX and NAV.</description></item><item><title>Backup and Restore of Dynamics 365 Instances</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/backup-restore-instance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/backup-restore-instance/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn This article is the last one about Dynamics instances. In this article, we will show you how to backup and restore an instance.
Backing up an instance In Dynamics 365, backups are automatically taken on a per-instance basis.
The frequency of acquisition is once a day, and the backup retention period is 3 days (maximum). Expired backups will be deleted automatically.
Obtain backups manually (on-demand backups) If you want to make a backup manually, click &amp;ldquo;New Backup&amp;rdquo; to make a backup.</description></item><item><title>Create sales proposals from leads in Project Service</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/dynamics-psa-lead-to-opportunity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/dynamics-psa-lead-to-opportunity/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Now that we have completed the structure and configuration of Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation (PSA), let&amp;rsquo;s create a project and start managing it.
How to create a project As a review of the previous article, the process of creating a project involves the creation of company and contact information from the lead, as well as a sales case. If the quote created from the sales proposal is accepted, a project contract is created, and the project begins.</description></item><item><title>Dynamics 365 for Marketing Free Edition Setup [2019.04]</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/marketing-with-dynamics-365/d365-marketing-trials-setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/marketing-with-dynamics-365/d365-marketing-trials-setup/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn We have already explained how to use the free version of Dynamics 365. In the past, Marketing was listed in this list of free versions, but now it is not. I contacted Microsoft, and they seem to be offering the free version of Marketing at a different URL, so here is the procedure.
The free version of the Marketing URL is a temporary measure and may become unavailable without announcement.</description></item><item><title>Dynamics 365 Security Basic Settings</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/basic-security-settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/basic-security-settings/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Now that we have added a user in Dynamics 365, let&amp;rsquo;s understand the basic security structure and settings. Dynamics 365 has the following security structure.
Departments and teams are groups of organizations, and you can manage organization groups in detail by adding users within them. Security Roles and Field Security are used to control access rights. *In this section, we will introduce them. Field security will be introduced in another article.</description></item><item><title>Let's take advantage of the sales functions of Dynamics 365.</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-sales-functions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-sales-functions/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn So far, I have explained the features for administrators, but now I would like to introduce the features for sales and marketing.
First of all, in Dynamics 365 for sales, there are two default entities, one for sales and one for marketing. Depending on the stage of your business, the entities you use will differ depending on whether you are focusing on marketing activities to acquire potential customers or sales activities to potential customers to advance the sales process to a contract.</description></item><item><title>Let's think about the implementation schedule and procedures for Dynamics 365</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/implementing-dynamics-365/deployment-schedule-dynamics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/implementing-dynamics-365/deployment-schedule-dynamics/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Once the purpose of implementing CRM and Dynamics 365 is clarified, it will be easier to consider the next step, which is how soon to implement them.
In the process of clarifying the purpose of implementing Dynamics 365, you may have made a list of both &amp;ldquo;need to be able to&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;want to be able to&amp;rdquo; operations.
It is important to consider the implementation schedule.</description></item><item><title>Linking Dynamics 365 and Yammer for interactive information exchange</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/dynamics365-with-yammer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/dynamics365-with-yammer/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn One of the features of Dynamics 365 for external system integration is the integration with Yammer; if you are using Yammer internally, you can use it with Dynamics 365 to actively exchange information about customers and business meetings internally.
What is Yammer? Yammer is, simply put, an internal social network. By setting access rights by company organizational unit, information can be exchanged securely. It can also be linked to SharePoint, so it is possible to share documents and minutes used in meetings across related departments within the company.</description></item><item><title>Set XRM ToolBox to hide the sitemap</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/hide-setting-sitemap-by-xrmtoolbox/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/hide-setting-sitemap-by-xrmtoolbox/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In this article, I will show you how to use a third party customization tool called XRM ToolBox to make the &amp;ldquo;Settings&amp;rdquo; sitemap visible only to users with administrative privileges.
Important note: XRM ToolBox is a Dynamics development tool that is introduced in the Japan Microsoft Dynamics 365 Team Blog. If you wish to use it, please do so at your own risk after thorough verification. Please note that we are not responsible for any damages caused by the contents of this site.</description></item><item><title>Why should you choose Dynamics 365?</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/understanding-dynamics-365/crm-dynamics-reason/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/understanding-dynamics-365/crm-dynamics-reason/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous Understanding CRM Systems article, you learned about CRM, why you need it, and the value of centralizing your information. If you are considering implementing a CRM system, I recommend Dynamics 365 from Microsoft. So why should you choose Dynamics 365? Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at why you should choose Dynamics 365.
What is Dynamics 365? Before recommending Dynamics 365 as a CRM system, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at what Dynamics 365 is.</description></item><item><title>Create a project in the Project Service</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/dynamics-psa-create-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/dynamics-psa-create-project/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn This is a continuation of the previous article, where we created a sales case from a lead in Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation (Project Service), and now we are going to create a project.
Create estimates from sales projects After a series of negotiations with prospective customers, we have entered the last quotation phase in the negotiations. The quotation is created within the sales project. This is the same as in the case of Sales.</description></item><item><title>Dealing with inability to send and receive Marketing emails (free version)</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/marketing-with-dynamics-365/cannot-send-email-from-trial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/marketing-with-dynamics-365/cannot-send-email-from-trial/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn I have found a problem in sending and receiving marketing emails using Dynamics 365 for Marketing free version.
Test transmissions are not received. When I created a marketing email in Dynamics 365 for Marketing and clicked &amp;ldquo;Test Send&amp;rdquo;, the email was not received by the appropriate email address.
Check your Dynamics 365 email settings. As a basic rule of thumb, make sure that you can send and receive emails in Dynamics 365.</description></item><item><title>Features of the Dynamics 365 application</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/understanding-dynamics-365/dynamics365-types-application/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/understanding-dynamics-365/dynamics365-types-application/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous article, I have explained why I recommend Dynamics 365 as a CRM system. In that article, I mentioned some of the applications available in Dynamics 365. In this section, I will introduce each application, starting from the sales support system to marketing, support services, project management, and human resources.
Sales support with Dynamics 365 for Sales Dynamics 365 for Sales is the most popular application in Dynamics 365.</description></item><item><title>Importing data into Dynamics 365</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/how-to-import-data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/how-to-import-data/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Once you have Dynamics 365 set up, it is time to import data. There are several ways to import data, but this article will discuss how to prepare the imported data and perform the import process.
Preparing for Data Import First, there are two ways to import data in Dynamics 365.
The first is to import using an Excel template for import. The other way is to import the data in Excel Online.</description></item><item><title>Integrate Dynamics 365 and Power Bi to enhance dashboards</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/create-powerbi-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/create-powerbi-dashboard/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Dynamics 365 has an existing dashboard function, but if you integrate Power BI, you will be able to check information more graphically.
Power BI is a business intelligence tool provided by Microsoft. It is a tool that processes large amounts of data and provides visualized information that is effective for business.
For more information, see What is Power BI? for more information. Also, Power BI Pro is available as a free trial version, so please take advantage of it.</description></item><item><title>Launching a Process in a Dynamics 365 Batch</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/use-batch-process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/use-batch-process/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In this case, we&amp;rsquo;re using a solution from Microsoft Labs. This section describes how to execute Dynamics 365 workflows in batch processing at a specified time.
Important note: If you wish to use the Change Tracking Solution in your own environment, please do so at your own risk after thorough verification. Please note that we cannot be held responsible for any damages caused by the contents of this website.</description></item><item><title>Let's try to use Dynamics 365 leads.</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-lead-entity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-lead-entity/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Now, we will use the Dynamics 365 sales entity while weaving in the previous scenario.
First, log in to Dynamics 365 and open Leads in the Sales area.
The following is a sample, but it shows the leads that are currently in progress (your open leads).
If you actually open one lead, you will see a screen like the one below. We will manage customer data, known as potential customers, in Leads.</description></item><item><title>Purchasing a Dynamics 365 license</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/implementing-dynamics-365/purchase-license-dynamics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/implementing-dynamics-365/purchase-license-dynamics/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn So far, we have been preparing for the implementation of Dynamics 365.
Now that we have a schedule and a rough estimate of the cost, we would like to start using Dynamics 365. The first thing you need to do is to purchase a license. This is very basic, but if you don&amp;rsquo;t purchase a license, you can&amp;rsquo;t proceed.
Purchase a license for Dynamics 365 First, proceed to purchase a license from the following website.</description></item><item><title>Update your Dynamics 365!</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/update-dynamics-instance-to-ver9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/update-dynamics-instance-to-ver9/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn It has been a while since Dynamcis 365 version 9 (July 2017 update) was released in July 2017. The trial version of Dynamcis 365 is now version 9, and those who are using version 8 may be in the minority. I think the number of people using version 8 is getting smaller.
As a matter of fact, my client&amp;rsquo;s Dynamics 365 was running on version 8 until recently.</description></item><item><title>Configure Dynamics 365 Field Security</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/set-security-field-profile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/set-security-field-profile/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn We have talked about security in terms of roles, departments, and teams. I think it&amp;rsquo;s safe to say that this knowledge is enough to set up security in your company.
However, what if more detailed security settings are required in the process of operating the system? For example, even within the same department, there are situations where detailed security settings are required, such as hiding or prohibiting the writing of information in each field.</description></item><item><title>Creating a Dynamics 365 Process</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/dynamics-365-process-use/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/dynamics-365-process-use/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Dynamics 365 has a feature called Processes that allows you to model your business methods and automate specific processes. There are four main types of processes. (The following is taken from the technical information)
Workflow. Use this process to model and automate real-world business processes. These processes can be configured to run in the background or in real time, and can require user input as needed. Workflow processes can be started automatically based on specified criteria or manually by the user.</description></item><item><title>Creating a Sales Case from a Lead in Dynamics 365</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/create-opportunity-from-lead/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/create-opportunity-from-lead/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous article, we talked about Leads in Dynamics 365. When a Lead becomes a Prospect, we will explain how to create a Client Company, a Client Representative, and a Sales Case from the Lead.
Assigning leads as potential. First, open a lead that you plan to discuss in the future. Then click on the &amp;ldquo;Prospect and Evaluate&amp;rdquo; button.
A duplicate check dialog will appear. If you already have a business relationship with a company and the contact person is the same, you can enter the company name and contact person name here.</description></item><item><title>Dynamics 365 Extensions - Workflow Tools</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/dynamics-solution-workflow-tools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/dynamics-solution-workflow-tools/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn I would like to introduce you to Dynamics 365 Workflow Tools, which greatly extends the functionality of Dynamics 365 Workflow. This is a great way to use the solution that I previously recommended in What is the best third party solution?
Important note: Dynamics 365 Workflow Tools is a third party solution. If you wish to use them in your own environment, please verify them thoroughly and use them at your own risk.</description></item><item><title>Five important decisions to make before implementing Dynamics 365</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/understanding-dynamics-365/5-keys-deploying-dynamics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/understanding-dynamics-365/5-keys-deploying-dynamics/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Now that you understand the various applications provided by Dynamics 365, you can use Dynamics 365 not only for SFA but also for HR, accounting, marketing and project management. Dynamics 365 can be used not only for SFA but also for HR, accounting, marketing and project management.
However, in this article, I would like to share something that you must be aware of before implementing Dynamics 365.</description></item><item><title>Plan your project with Project Service</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/plan-project-schedule-resource/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/plan-project-schedule-resource/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Now that we have completed the creation of the previous project, let&amp;rsquo;s fill in the contents of the project. When a project starts, a project plan is generally prepared with the following structure.
Project Objectives and Goals Scope (range) Schedule Cost System (Resources) Communication Quality Management Lists and countermeasures Reference: Can a PM beginner do it? How to make a project plan
In this article, we will use the WBS and Schedule Board of Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation.</description></item><item><title>Retrieve data from on-premises SQL Server</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/getting-data-from-on-premise-sql/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/getting-data-from-on-premise-sql/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Dynamics 365 can be integrated with PowerApps, Flow, and Power BI, called Power Platform, to further enhance its value. If you have a Dynamics 365 Customer Engagement Plan license, you should definitely take advantage of this application.
Currently, Dynamics 365 uses the Common Data Service to manage data, so data stored in Dynamics 365 can be seamlessly passed to PowerApps, Flow, and Power BI, which also use the Common Data Service.</description></item><item><title>About Dynamics 365 Hierarchical Security Settings</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/use-security-hierarchy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/use-security-hierarchy/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In addition to security roles that control security on a per-entity basis, field security on a per-field basis, and department and team security for managing user affiliations, Dynamics 365 has an evolving security concept called hierarchical security.
Hierarchical security settings are not enabled by default, but the steps we will show you will allow you to configure them.
What you can do with hierarchical security With hierarchical security, even if a user&amp;rsquo;s access privileges to an entity are set to &amp;ldquo;user only&amp;rdquo; (can only access their own records), they can still view and edit the data of users below them in the hierarchy, which is a big advantage of keeping the security role settings simple and expanding the access range.</description></item><item><title>Basic operation of Dynamics 365 processes</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-more-of-workflow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-more-of-workflow/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous article, &amp;ldquo;Creating a Process in Dynamics 365&amp;rdquo;, we have discussed the steps to create a workflow for a process.
Update the record In the previous article, we gave you a simple way to update records, so this time we will apply it.
Update the value of the associated record This is done by changing the entity to be updated after adding the step of updating the record.</description></item><item><title>Exporting Dynamics 365 data to Azure SQL</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/exporting-d365data-to-azuresql/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/exporting-d365data-to-azuresql/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn We will show you how to export Dynamics 365 data to Azure SQL Server using an add-on service called Data Export Service.
Although Dynamics 365 provides data recovery by tracking data changes through audit history and restoring instances through date/time backups, there was no convenient way to restore deleted data other than using XRM Toolbox, so the Data Export Service is very useful.
The procedure for setting up the Data Export Service is described in the official document Replicating Data in an Azure SQL Database, but the procedure for generating the Key Vault URL was not done correctly by reading the document alone, so I decided to summarize it this time by adding the contents of my research.</description></item><item><title>Project Service Manage and close projects</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/manage-and-close-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/manage-and-close-project/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In this article, you will learn how to plan a project in Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation. Once the plan is made, the project will be started. In this section, we will introduce the steps to manage a project.
Estimated cost management After the project members are selected from the resources and assigned to each WBS, the estimated labor cost is automatically calculated according to the WBS.</description></item><item><title>Use Dynamics 365 activities to conduct business meetings.</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/p1036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/p1036/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous article, we created a sales case from a lead, and we need to keep track of the progress of the negotiation in the sales case. In this case, we can use an entity called activity.
Type of activity entity First, in Dynamics 365, there is an entity called Activity (Activity Pointer). These activities are associated with various entities such as client companies, contacts, sales projects, leads, support projects, etc.</description></item><item><title>Using Dynamics 365 for Outlook</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/dynamics365-app-for-outlook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/integrating-dynamics-365-with-other-systems/dynamics365-app-for-outlook/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn One of the most useful features of Dynamics 365 is its integration with Outlook.
If you are an Outlook user, you can check your Dynamics customer and case information and update your activity information directly from Outlook.
You can also update your activity information, so if you are already using Office 365, there is no reason not to use it.
There are some things you need to do to use Dynamics 365 for Outlook.</description></item><item><title>What is the purpose of implementing Dynamics 365 and what goals do you want to achieve?</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/understanding-dynamics-365/whats-your-goal-by-dynamics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/understanding-dynamics-365/whats-your-goal-by-dynamics/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous article, I introduced the five points that you should decide before implementing Dynamics 365. In this article, I would like to focus on the &amp;ldquo;purpose&amp;rdquo; of the implementation. In this article, we will discuss the &amp;ldquo;purpose of the implementation&amp;rdquo;.　Determining the &amp;ldquo;purpose&amp;rdquo; of the implementation is to determine how Dynamics 365 will serve as a system for your company and how it will benefit the company as a whole.</description></item><item><title>Instructions for using the Dynamics 365 free trial version [as of 2018].</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/understanding-dynamics-365/how-to-use-dynamics-trial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/understanding-dynamics-365/how-to-use-dynamics-trial/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn If you are still considering to introduce Dynamics 365, I recommend you to try the free trial version to get a better understanding of the usability and operation. In particular, the Dynamics 365 blog provides detailed information about the functions, uses, and setup procedures of each Dynamics 365 application, so it is an important step to deepen your understanding by actually touching it with your own hands.</description></item><item><title>Leverage Dynamics 365 trading partners and trading counterparts</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/utilize-account-and-contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/utilize-account-and-contact/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Now that I have told you about the sales projects and related activities, I will mention the parent entity, the client company and the client representative.
Relationships between client companies and upper and lower levels The client company, or company name, is the parent entity (higher-level entity) for client personnel, sales projects, and activities. In other words, based on the information of the client company, the information of the child entities (subordinate entities) is created and associated with it.</description></item><item><title>Project Service resource allocation and shipping units</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/psa-assign-team-members/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/psa-assign-team-members/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn When you create a project in Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation and assign team members, the calculation of the assigned time for the assigned members is a bit complicated, so I will show you how it works.
Resource &amp;ldquo;allocation method&amp;rdquo;. When you assign resources as a team member of a project, you have a choice in the field called &amp;ldquo;Assignment Method&amp;rdquo;.
If you check the official page, you will see that it means the following.</description></item><item><title>Ribbon Workbench: Show and Hide Buttons by Field Value</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/ribbon-workbench-hide-button-with-field-value/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/customizing-dynamics-365/ribbon-workbench-hide-button-with-field-value/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn You can use Ribbon Workbench to show or hide the buttons.
However, if you simply want to hide unnecessary buttons, you can do so by adjusting the permissions in the security role.
So this time, we will add a setting to show or hide the field depending on its value.
advance preparation Before doing any customization, do some advance preparation.
Importing Ribbon Workbench Ribbon Workbench can be downloaded from RIBBON WORKBENCH.</description></item><item><title>Using Dynamics 365 business rules</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-business-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-business-rules/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Dynamics 365 has a feature called Business Rules. Normally, Javascript implementation is required to hide fields or perform operations according to conditions on a form. However, this feature eliminates the need for script implementation and allows users to easily set up the rules required for their business.
The following can be achieved with business rules.
By combining conditions and actions, business rules can be used to perform the following operations</description></item><item><title>Using the Dynamics 365 Portal Add-on</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/use-dynamics-portal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/use-dynamics-portal/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn The Dynamics 365 Customer Engagement Plan application comes standard with one portal add-on.
The advantages of using a portal include the following
Provide services and information using Dynamics 365 data to users outside the organization who do not have a license to use Dynamics 365. Web services can be easily built by simply creating and editing Dynamics 365 records. You can easily build web services by simply creating and editing Dynamics 365 records.</description></item><item><title>Configuring Dynamics 365 Apps</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/dynamics-setting-application/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/dynamics-setting-application/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In this section, we will talk a little bit about Dynamics 365 applications.
In Dynamics 365, a new feature called &amp;ldquo;Applications&amp;rdquo; is available, which allows users to set access permissions based on their security roles.
Right after the installation of Dynamics 365, default applications, sales, services, etc. are created. For example, you can manage the sales force in your company by giving them access to an application called Sales, so that they do not see unnecessary entities or data in advance.</description></item><item><title>Managing Dynamics 365 Entities</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/create-new-entity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/create-new-entity/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Learn how to manage Dynamics 365 entities, including creating, editing, and deleting them.
About Entities When you set up Dynamics 365, you are provided with basic entities such as customer company, customer representative, sales case, and activities. Each entity manages company information, representative information, business meetings, and activities of business meetings (phone calls, emails, appointments, tasks, etc.).
It also allows you to create custom entities for your organization and associate them with default entities for flexible management of your business data.</description></item><item><title>Scenarios for using Dynamics 365 in sales</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/understanding-dynamics-365/use-scenario-dynamics-sales/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/understanding-dynamics-365/use-scenario-dynamics-sales/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn The purpose of implementing Dynamics 365 has become clearer, and with the cooperation of each department, we are now able to visualize to some extent the follow-up system after implementation.
Now that the decision to implement Dynamics 365 has been made in the company, you need to convey the image of starting to use Dynamics 365 to your main sales members.
We have already talked about what Dynamics 365 can do, but what would happen if salespeople actually used the features?</description></item><item><title>Troubleshoot PSA Schedule Board</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/psa-troubleshoot-schedule-board/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/psa-troubleshoot-schedule-board/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn As I mentioned when I planned a project in Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation (PSA), Project Service seems to behave differently depending on the interface and version differences.
It may be possible to improve this by upgrading the version, but here are the steps we took to deal with it in version 2 first.
*This will be available as of January 2019.
Background: Moving to a unified interface The menu that you are used to in version 8 of Dynamics 365 is called the Web Interface, but in version 9, a new interface called the Unified Interface has been added that is also mobile friendly.</description></item><item><title>Use the email tracking feature</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/sales-insights-email-tracking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/sales-insights-email-tracking/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Dynamics 365 for Sales includes the ability to track opens, link clicks, and attachments to emails sent to customers, which is great because Salesforce requires you to purchase Pardot separately, but it&amp;rsquo;s available at no extra cost!
Reference Technical Information
Using Email Engagement to View Message Interactions
The setup is very simple, so I will summarize the steps.
Setting up an email profile Set up an email profile so that you can send emails in Dynamics.</description></item><item><title>Boost your sales force with Dynamics 365 product catalogs</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-catalog-for-sales/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-catalog-for-sales/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn So far, we have discussed how to manage sales deals that have been rated as &amp;ldquo;promising&amp;rdquo; by the lead.
In this article, I would like to explain how to manage the products that are important for sales projects on Dynamics 365.
The products that are important to the sales process are called product catalogs, and they allow you to manage what products are available (product families), in what units they are shipped (shipping unit list), and at what discount rates (discount and price lists) to generate quotes and invoices.</description></item><item><title>Editing WBS in Project Service and Microsoft Project</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/editing-wbs-by-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/editing-wbs-by-project/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn By integrating Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation with Microsoft Project, you can edit WBS on a client terminal. In this article, we will show you how to integrate them.
*This article assumes that you already have Microsoft Project installed on your device. If you have not installed it yet, please install it from the Microsoft 365 Management Center as shown below.
Install Microsoft Project If you have an Office 365 subscription, you can install Microsoft Project from Office 365.</description></item><item><title>How to deal with Dynamics 365 import errors</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/dynamics-import-error/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/dynamics-import-error/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous article, we have shown you how to import data using Excel template, but if an error occurs during data import, what should you do?
When do I get an error? First of all, the most common error in the template is due to duplicate data, as you can see in the Excel template, the value of the reference field is entered based on the display name.</description></item><item><title>Scenarios for using Dynamics 365 in marketing</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/understanding-dynamics-365/marketing-use-scenario/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/understanding-dynamics-365/marketing-use-scenario/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the scenario of using Dynamics 365 in sales, we introduced a scenario of using Dynamics 365 in sales. Now, what would happen if Dynamics 365 is used in marketing? Nowadays, more than sales activities, how to effectively conduct marketing activities to increase the number of potential customers is becoming an indispensable part of a company&amp;rsquo;s survival strategy.
In this scenario, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at a scenario in which two applications, Dynamics 365 for Sales and Dynamics 365 for Marketing, are used to perform marketing activities.</description></item><item><title>Using Dynamics 365 Calculated Fields</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-calculation-fields/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-calculation-fields/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In this article, I will give a brief introduction to calculated fields in Dynamics 365.
About calculated fields Calculated fields are a type of field in Dynamics 365 that can be used for the following data types
One line of text Option Set Two options integer decimal number Currency Date and time By using calculated fields, you can change the value of a field depending on the condition of If Else, calculate it by a function, or get the data of a related entity via a lookup field.</description></item><item><title>Create Dynamics 365 product families and bundles</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/product-family-bundle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/product-family-bundle/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous article, we created a single product and even a discount table. In this article, we will configure a product family and associate a product to the family. We will now discuss how to use product families.
Create a product family A product family is used to manage a group of similar products together. For example, there is a parent family of products called PCs, which can be divided into notebooks, desktops, and tablets as its child families.</description></item><item><title>Data import in Dynamics 365 Excel Online</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/import-data-from-excel-online/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/configure-initial-settings-for-dynamics-365/import-data-from-excel-online/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous article, we introduced the process of importing data using an import template. This method can be very useful when importing initial data. In this article, I will describe how to import data dynamically in Excel Online based on the view you have created instead of using a template.
Note that you do not need to have Excel client installed on your local PC to edit dynamically in Excel Online.</description></item><item><title>Managing a Dynamics 365 Instance</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/manage-dynamics-instance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/manage-dynamics-instance/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at what you can do in the Dynamics 365 admin center.
Managing Instances Instances allow you to manage the currently configured instances (production and sandbox (*1)) and install solutions for the instances. In the case of Plan 1 license, a free sandbox instance is provided.
(*2)
(*1) What is a sandbox?
A sandbox instance is a non-production environment instance of Microsoft Dynamics 365 (online).</description></item><item><title>Update the Project Service working template</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/psa-update-work-template/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/managing-projects-in-dynamics-365/psa-update-work-template/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn This section provides instructions on how to update a work template in Dynamics 365 for Project Service Automation.In the previous section, &amp;ldquo;Planning a Project with Project Service&amp;rdquo;, we showed you how to create a work template, but this is the procedure to follow if you want to change the holidays, operating hours, etc. of a work template that has already been set up.
How to update the working template After setting up the work templates you have already created for your resources and projects, you may need to update them by adding holidays or changing the operating hours due to various factors.</description></item><item><title>Customization of Dynamics 365 entities and option sets</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/customize-entity-option-sets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/customize-entity-option-sets/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn From the Dynamics 365 menu, click on Settings - Customize System to open the Solution Explorer as shown below.
Then expand Components and you will see a customizable list.
Let&amp;rsquo;s discuss some of the typical components here.
entity The first one is Entities, where you can configure basic entity-related settings. If you expand the &amp;ldquo;Entities&amp;rdquo; component, you will see a list of default entities. (Left side of the screen below)</description></item><item><title>Manage properties of Dynamics products</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/properties-of-product/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/properties-of-product/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn The following is a continuation of the previous article on product properties.
You can now create and use a complete Dynamics 365 product to price list. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at the products in more detail.
In the products that we offer, there are many different attributes and conditions. For example, in the case of cell phone cases, we need to classify the color, shape, size, available cell phone models, and condition (new or used).</description></item><item><title>Customize Dynamics 365 web resources and processes</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/customize-web-resource-process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/customize-web-resource-process/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In the previous article, we talked about &amp;ldquo;entities&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;option sets&amp;rdquo; rather than system customization. What other customizations can be done?
In this article, I will provide an overview of web resources, processes, dashboards, and reports.
Web Resources Web resources can be used to create HTML files, Javascript, CSS, XML and Silverlight applications, as well as image files such as icons for Dynamics 365. The content you create with web resources can be used in forms, sitemaps, etc.</description></item><item><title>Get the upper hand in negotiations with a Dynamics 365 discount table</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-discount-price-lists/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-discount-price-lists/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn With the product families we have created previously, we can now manage our sales case records more efficiently. Now, there will come a time when you need to adjust the final price of the deal. This is where the discount table comes into play.
We have already created a discount table in a previous article, so we will actually use this function.
Publish product families, products, and bundles The first step is to publish the product family, product, and bundle that you created in the previous article.</description></item><item><title>Leveraging cross-selling and up-selling of Dynamics 365 products</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-up-cross-sell-sales/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-up-cross-sell-sales/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In sales activities, up-selling and cross-selling are necessary activities to increase customer profitability.
Up-selling is a sales activity in which you sell your product or service as something higher and more expensive, while cross-selling is a sales activity in which you sell a combination of products and services related to the product or service you are selling.
In the properties of the online-only license, we had previously created that the segment was set up.</description></item><item><title>Recommended third-party solutions</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/whats-3rd-party-solutions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/whats-3rd-party-solutions/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn The beauty of Dynamics 365 is that there are many solutions available to assist and augment its functionality, but what solutions can further extend the capabilities of Dynamics 365?
In this article, I would like to introduce some of the solutions I have used that have been particularly effective after installation.
(*Note) Third-party solutions are not necessarily solutions that Microsoft guarantees to work. This blog is only for information sharing, so please import at your own risk with sufficient verification when importing in your own environment.</description></item><item><title>Countermeasures against infinite loops in workflow processes</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-workflow-process-loop/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-workflow-process-loop/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn The workflow process in Dynamics 365 is a useful feature that allows you to do many things without coding, from updating, creating and deleting data to assigning and sending emails. In addition to the default workflow processes, you can import third-party workflow solutions such as those found in Workflow Heroes, which allow you to create workflow processes for many of your users&amp;rsquo; needs, such as record sharing, date and decimal arithmetic, and more.</description></item><item><title>Manage everything from estimates to invoices with Dynamics 365</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/create-estimate-invoice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/create-estimate-invoice/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn So far, we have discussed sales projects and products in detail. If the business meeting goes well, we will prepare a quotation for the customer. If the quotation is accepted, the sales case is put in the &amp;ldquo;order&amp;rdquo; status, and an invoice is prepared and submitted to the customer.
I will now show you how to perform this process in Dynamics 365 for Sales.
Create a quote from a sales project.</description></item><item><title>Changes to the method of applying major updates [2019.08]</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/changed_update_policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/changed_update_policy/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn To be honest, I think the major update of Dynamics 365 is an update that makes the operation and maintenance department cry.
To support the update
Wait for the instance to become eligible for updates. Once an instance is eligible for an update, set a candidate update date for verification in the sandbox. Make two schedules to prepare for the case that the proposed date does not run as planned.</description></item><item><title>Using Graphs in Dynamics 365</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-dynamics-graph/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-dynamics-graph/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn By using Dynamics 365 and continuing to effectively manage your sales activities, you will accumulate enough data in Dynamics 365 to consider your sales strategy.
You can use the data to help you determine what activities and sales talks are effective, research ways to approach different types of customers, and offer new products and services to win business.
What is even more remarkable is that Dynamics 365 allows you to process and visualize the data in reports, graphs, and dashboards based on the accumulated corporate data.</description></item><item><title>Adjust the sitemap in the settings</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-privilege-to-settingsitemap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/maintaining-dynamics-365/use-privilege-to-settingsitemap/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn When you create a Dynamics 365 app, it will be created as a unified interface (mobile-driven app) due to the current integration with Power Apps. This is where the advanced settings can be opened to the general public, but I found out that the settings can be fine-tuned, so I will describe them here.
Settings menu visible to the general public Even ordinary users with little to no privileges can use</description></item><item><title>Managing Leads with Sales Funnels in Dynamics 365</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/manage-lead-by-sales-funnel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/manage-lead-by-sales-funnel/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In this article, I would like to talk about the &amp;ldquo;Sales Funnel&amp;rdquo;, which I mentioned in the section &amp;ldquo;Using Graphs in Dynamics 365&amp;rdquo;.
Let&amp;rsquo;s start by understanding what a sales funnel is, and then let&amp;rsquo;s actually create a sales funnel based on the data of potential customers called leads.
What is a sales funnel? Funnel means &amp;ldquo;funnel,&amp;rdquo; and is a device used for pouring liquid or powder into a container with a small diameter.</description></item><item><title>Managing Goals in Dynamics 365</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/create-sales-target-and-goal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/create-sales-target-and-goal/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn In this article, we will talk about goals in Dynamics 365. In Dynamics 365, you can define goal indicators to manage your goals.
The following technical information is quoted as describing the function of goal management.
&amp;quot; The functions of goal management are as follows
Create a complex goal hierarchy. In this hierarchy, individual goal contributors or teams are assigned their own goals. Use goals in the hierarchy to track important business data (sales, customer service support cases, phone calls, etc.</description></item><item><title>Visualize information in the Dynamics 365 dashboard</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-dynamics-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/use-dynamics-dashboard/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn I have been informing you about the sales features of Dynamics 365. Now that you understand graphs, funnels, and goal management, let&amp;rsquo;s touch on dashboards.
There are two types of dashboards in Dynamics 365: system dashboards and user dashboards. The user dashboard allows you to visualize information by editing records that you have permissions for in graphs, grids, and lists.
In addition, system administrators can create system dashboards, which can be made public and configured for company-wide or departmental use.</description></item><item><title>Analyze data with Dynamics 365 reporting functions</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/analyze-data-by-reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/analyze-data-by-reports/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Dynamics 365 allows users to generate fetch-based reports using the Report Wizard. This feature can be used by users to collect and analyze data in a simplified manner.
How to create a report Creating a report is simple. First, click &amp;ldquo;Reports&amp;rdquo; from the menu.
Click the &amp;ldquo;+ New&amp;rdquo; button to create a new report.
Click &amp;ldquo;Report Wizard&amp;rdquo; to start creating a report.
If you want to create a new report, check the &amp;ldquo;Start a new report&amp;rdquo; box and click &amp;ldquo;Next&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Track the latest activity on your Dynamics 365 wall</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/trace-activities-by-wall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/trace-activities-by-wall/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn When I introduced the Dynamics 365 dashboard, I mentioned the wall.
In this article, I would like to post on the wall. when you open the Dynamics 365 home page, you will be taken to the default dashboard page, where the wall posts the status of each entity and allows you to track the active activities.
For example, when a new business partner company is created, when a competitor for a sales project is created, when an order is received or lost, etc.</description></item><item><title>Create a quote with Word template</title><link>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/create-quote-by-word-template/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://andaze.com/dynamics365/en/supporting-sales-with-dynamics-365/create-quote-by-word-template/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Here is a summary of the steps to create your own quote using the Word template.
advance preparation The first step is to create a sales case and add some products to be used in the quote. In this case, we added two products to the sales case and created a quote in advance with the tax amount added as well.
The total amount is as follows.</description></item></channel></rss>