<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dynamics-365-for-marketing on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/marketing-with-dynamics-365/</link><description>Recent content in dynamics-365-for-marketing on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/marketing-with-dynamics-365/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setting up Dynamics 365 for Marketing</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/marketing-with-dynamics-365/dynamics-365-for-marketing-setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/marketing-with-dynamics-365/dynamics-365-for-marketing-setup/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn Have you ever heard of a marketing support application called Dynamics 365 for Marketing?
Dynamics 365 for Marketing is an application that allows you to analyze how effective your marketing efforts are in reaching potential customers who have received information from your company&amp;rsquo;s website, blog, mail magazines, or who have attended your seminars or events.
Originally, Marketing was a marketing function associated with Sales that could be used mainly for sending campaign emails.</description></item><item><title>Dynamics 365 for Marketing Free Edition Setup [2019.04]</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/marketing-with-dynamics-365/d365-marketing-trials-setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/marketing-with-dynamics-365/d365-marketing-trials-setup/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn We have already explained how to use the free version of Dynamics 365. In the past, Marketing was listed in this list of free versions, but now it is not. I contacted Microsoft, and they seem to be offering the free version of Marketing at a different URL, so here is the procedure.
The free version of the Marketing URL is a temporary measure and may become unavailable without announcement.</description></item><item><title>Dealing with inability to send and receive Marketing emails (free version)</title><link>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/marketing-with-dynamics-365/cannot-send-email-from-trial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dev.andaze.com/dynamics365/en/marketing-with-dynamics-365/cannot-send-email-from-trial/</guid><description>Author:Takafumi Noguchi
linkedIn I have found a problem in sending and receiving marketing emails using Dynamics 365 for Marketing free version.
Test transmissions are not received. When I created a marketing email in Dynamics 365 for Marketing and clicked &amp;ldquo;Test Send&amp;rdquo;, the email was not received by the appropriate email address.
Check your Dynamics 365 email settings. As a basic rule of thumb, make sure that you can send and receive emails in Dynamics 365.</description></item></channel></rss>